<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>marker - Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks &amp; More</title>
	<atom:link href="/new-bjhlpy-tag/marker/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Discover Turkey’s cities, historical sites, and landscapes on Google Maps. Easily navigate through Istanbul, Cappadocia, Antalya, and beyond with interactive maps and street views.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 17:53:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Navigating The Florida Keys: Understanding The Mile Marker System</title>
		<link>/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-florida-keys-understanding-the-mile-marker-system-rbhkdc-pics/</link>
					<comments>/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-florida-keys-understanding-the-mile-marker-system-rbhkdc-pics/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[2025]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[florida]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[keys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[navigating]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[system]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[understanding]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://w1.geleleger.nl/navigating-the-florida-keys-understanding-the-mile-marker-system/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Navigating the Florida Keys: Understanding the Mile Marker System Related Articles: Navigating the Florida Keys: [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-florida-keys-understanding-the-mile-marker-system-rbhkdc-pics/">Navigating The Florida Keys: Understanding The Mile Marker System</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Navigating the Florida Keys: Understanding the Mile Marker System</p>
<h2 id="related-articles:-navigating-the-florida-keys:-understanding-the-mile-marker-system">Related Articles: Navigating the Florida Keys: Understanding the Mile Marker System</h2>
<h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2>
<p>With enthusiasm, let&#8217;s navigate through the intriguing topic related to Navigating the Florida Keys: Understanding the Mile Marker System. Let&#8217;s weave interesting information and offer fresh perspectives to the readers.</p>
<div id="toc">
<h2>Table of Content</h2>
<ul>
<li><a href="#related-articles:-navigating-the-florida-keys:-understanding-the-mile-marker-system">1 Related Articles: Navigating the Florida Keys: Understanding the Mile Marker System</a></li>
<li><a href="#introduction">2 Introduction</a></li>
<li><a href="#navigating-the-florida-keys:-understanding-the-mile-marker-system">3 Navigating the Florida Keys: Understanding the Mile Marker System</a></li>
<li><a href="#closure">4 Closure</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2 id="navigating-the-florida-keys:-understanding-the-mile-marker-system">Navigating the Florida Keys: Understanding the Mile Marker System</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://2.bp.blogspot.com/-jW3lInsXchk/TmnSac5l9eI/AAAAAAAAEvc/pn8FML1FHrw/s1600/Florida%2BKeys%2BMap%2B5.jpg" alt="Printable Map Florida Keys Mile Markers" /></p>
<p>The Florida Keys, a string of islands stretching south from mainland Florida, offer a unique and captivating travel experience. But amidst the turquoise waters, white-sand beaches, and vibrant marine life, navigating this archipelago can be a bit tricky. This is where the Florida Keys Mile Marker system comes into play, a crucial tool for navigating and experiencing the islands.</p>
<p><strong>The Mile Marker System: A Unique Navigational Tool</strong></p>
<p>The Florida Keys Mile Marker system is a unique and highly effective way of addressing locations along the Overseas Highway, the iconic road connecting the islands.  Unlike traditional street addresses, mile markers are numbered sequentially from the north (Key Largo) to the south (Key West), starting at MM 106 and ending at MM 0. </p>
<p>Each mile marker is a signpost positioned on the side of the Overseas Highway, displaying a number indicating the distance from Key Largo.  This system is used for everything from finding restaurants and attractions to identifying specific locations for boating and fishing.</p>
<p><strong>Benefits of the Mile Marker System</strong></p>
<p>The Mile Marker system offers numerous benefits for visitors and residents alike:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Simplified Navigation:</strong> The system provides a straightforward and intuitive way to navigate the Keys, eliminating the need for complicated street addresses.</li>
<li><strong>Precise Location Identification:</strong> Each mile marker represents a specific point on the Overseas Highway, making it easy to locate businesses, attractions, and even specific spots for fishing or snorkeling.</li>
<li><strong>Emergency Response:</strong> In case of an emergency, providing a mile marker location helps emergency services quickly locate the incident.</li>
<li><strong>Tourist Information:</strong> The mile marker system is a valuable tool for tourists, helping them find accommodation, restaurants, attractions, and other points of interest.</li>
<li><strong>Local Navigation:</strong> Residents use mile markers for everyday purposes, from finding the nearest grocery store to meeting friends at a specific location.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Understanding the Mile Marker System: A Guide for Travelers</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Odd vs. Even Numbers:</strong> Mile markers on the east side of the Overseas Highway are odd numbers, while those on the west side are even numbers.</li>
<li><strong>Key West as the Starting Point:</strong>  Mile markers count down as you drive south, with MM 0 marking the southernmost point of Key West.</li>
<li><strong>Navigational Tools:</strong>  Maps, GPS devices, and online resources like Google Maps are valuable tools for navigating the Keys using the mile marker system. </li>
<li><strong>Look for Signs:</strong> Pay attention to signs along the Overseas Highway that indicate mile marker numbers, especially when searching for specific locations.</li>
<li><strong>Use the System for Boat Navigation:</strong> The mile marker system extends to the waterways surrounding the Keys, helping boaters navigate and identify locations.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Examples of Mile Marker Use</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Finding a Restaurant:</strong> If you&#8217;re searching for a specific restaurant at MM 47, you can easily locate it by driving down the Overseas Highway until you reach the signpost indicating MM 47.</li>
<li><strong>Boat Launch:</strong>  Many boat ramps in the Keys are identified by mile markers, making it easy for boaters to find access points.</li>
<li><strong>Emergency Services:</strong> In case of an emergency, providing the mile marker location of the incident helps emergency services quickly dispatch help.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>FAQs about the Florida Keys Mile Marker System</strong></p>
<p><strong>Q: What is the purpose of the mile marker system?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> The mile marker system is a unique addressing system used in the Florida Keys to identify locations along the Overseas Highway. It provides a simple and effective way to navigate the islands and locate points of interest.</p>
<p><strong>Q: How does the mile marker system work?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Mile markers are numbered sequentially from north to south, starting at MM 106 in Key Largo and ending at MM 0 in Key West. Each marker is a signpost on the side of the Overseas Highway indicating the distance from Key Largo.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What is the difference between odd and even mile markers?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Odd-numbered mile markers are located on the east side of the Overseas Highway, while even-numbered mile markers are on the west side.</p>
<p><strong>Q: Can I use the mile marker system for boat navigation?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Yes, the mile marker system extends to the waterways surrounding the Keys, making it a useful tool for boat navigation.</p>
<p><strong>Q: Are there any resources available for learning more about the mile marker system?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Yes, numerous resources are available online and in printed guides, including maps, GPS devices, and online resources like Google Maps.</p>
<p><strong>Tips for Navigating the Florida Keys with Mile Markers</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Plan Your Route:</strong> Before embarking on your trip, plan your route using a map or GPS device that incorporates the mile marker system.</li>
<li><strong>Look for Signs:</strong> Pay close attention to mile marker signs along the Overseas Highway, especially when searching for specific locations.</li>
<li><strong>Use the System for Boat Navigation:</strong> If you&#8217;re planning to boat in the Keys, familiarize yourself with the mile marker system for waterways.</li>
<li><strong>Ask Locals:</strong> Don&#8217;t hesitate to ask locals for directions or help navigating the Keys. They are familiar with the mile marker system and can provide valuable insights.</li>
<li><strong>Keep a Map Handy:</strong>  Even with GPS, it&#8217;s always a good idea to keep a physical map of the Keys handy, especially if you&#8217;re venturing off the beaten path.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>
<p>The Florida Keys Mile Marker system is an essential tool for navigating the islands and experiencing all they offer. By understanding the system and utilizing it effectively, visitors and residents alike can navigate the Keys with ease, explore hidden gems, and enjoy the unique beauty of this island paradise. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://data.docslib.org/img/3237415/florida-keys-mile-marker-guide.jpg" alt="Florida Keys Mile-Marker Guide - DocsLib" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://3.bp.blogspot.com/-c7RZnDqOxjY/UMWRfBmTmwI/AAAAAAAABf4/0KSHaMxN7VY/s1600/map.png" alt="Printable Map Florida Keys Mile Markers" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://floridatravel.blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Florida-keys-map-with-mile-markers2.jpg" alt="Printable Map Florida Keys Mile Markers" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://i0.wp.com/itravelinn.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Florida-Keys-map.png?resize=768%2C493u0026ssl=1" alt="Florida Keys Travel Guide: Things to Do, Maps &#038; Food" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://activerain.com/image_store/uploads/1/3/6/4/1/ar129407585914631.jpg" alt="Mile Markers in The Florida KeysWhat do they Mean???" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://www.florida-backroads-travel.com/images/TheFloridaKeysMap.png" alt="Map Of The Florida Keys With Mile Markers - Polly Camellia" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="http://seaviewestate.net/images/map/Map_page_img.gif" alt="Florida Keys Map With Mile Markers - Maping Resources" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://printablemapforyou.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/florida-keys-aqueduct-authority-florida-keys-map-with-mile-markers.jpg" alt="Florida Keys Aqueduct Authority - Florida Keys Map With Mile Markers " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"></p>
<h2 id="closure">Closure</h2>
<p>Thus, we hope this article has provided valuable insights into Navigating the Florida Keys: Understanding the Mile Marker System. We appreciate your attention to our article. See you in our next article!</p><p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-florida-keys-understanding-the-mile-marker-system-rbhkdc-pics/">Navigating The Florida Keys: Understanding The Mile Marker System</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-florida-keys-understanding-the-mile-marker-system-rbhkdc-pics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Navigating The Grand Canyon State: A Guide To Arizona Mile Marker Maps</title>
		<link>/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-grand-canyon-state-a-guide-to-arizona-mile-marker-maps-rbhkdc-pics/</link>
					<comments>/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-grand-canyon-state-a-guide-to-arizona-mile-marker-maps-rbhkdc-pics/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 03:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[2025]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[arizona]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[canyon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[grand]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[guide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maps]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[marker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mile]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[navigating]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[state]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[to]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://w1.geleleger.nl/navigating-the-grand-canyon-state-a-guide-to-arizona-mile-marker-maps/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Navigating the Grand Canyon State: A Guide to Arizona Mile Marker Maps Related Articles: Navigating [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-grand-canyon-state-a-guide-to-arizona-mile-marker-maps-rbhkdc-pics/">Navigating The Grand Canyon State: A Guide To Arizona Mile Marker Maps</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Navigating the Grand Canyon State: A Guide to Arizona Mile Marker Maps</p>
<h2 id="related-articles:-navigating-the-grand-canyon-state:-a-guide-to-arizona-mile-marker-maps">Related Articles: Navigating the Grand Canyon State: A Guide to Arizona Mile Marker Maps</h2>
<h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2>
<p>With enthusiasm, let&#8217;s navigate through the intriguing topic related to Navigating the Grand Canyon State: A Guide to Arizona Mile Marker Maps. Let&#8217;s weave interesting information and offer fresh perspectives to the readers.</p>
<div id="toc">
<h2>Table of Content</h2>
<ul>
<li><a href="#related-articles:-navigating-the-grand-canyon-state:-a-guide-to-arizona-mile-marker-maps">1 Related Articles: Navigating the Grand Canyon State: A Guide to Arizona Mile Marker Maps</a></li>
<li><a href="#introduction">2 Introduction</a></li>
<li><a href="#navigating-the-grand-canyon-state:-a-guide-to-arizona-mile-marker-maps">3 Navigating the Grand Canyon State: A Guide to Arizona Mile Marker Maps</a></li>
<li><a href="#closure">4 Closure</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2 id="navigating-the-grand-canyon-state:-a-guide-to-arizona-mile-marker-maps">Navigating the Grand Canyon State: A Guide to Arizona Mile Marker Maps</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" src="http://npmaps.com/wp-content/uploads/grand-canyon-regional-map.jpg" alt="Navigating The Grand Canyon State: A Comprehensive Guide To Arizona’s " /></p>
<p>Arizona, a state renowned for its diverse landscapes, from the towering red rocks of Sedona to the majestic Grand Canyon, presents a unique challenge for travelers: navigating vast distances and diverse terrains. To aid in this endeavor, mile marker maps have become an indispensable tool for both residents and visitors. These maps, essentially visual guides along major roadways, provide crucial information that streamlines travel and ensures a safe and enjoyable journey.</p>
<p><strong>Understanding the Importance of Mile Marker Maps</strong></p>
<p>Mile marker maps are more than just visual representations of distances; they offer a comprehensive system for understanding and navigating Arizona&#8217;s extensive highway network. Each mile marker, a numbered sign placed along the roadside, provides a specific reference point, allowing travelers to:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Pinpoint Locations:</strong>  Identify exact locations along a highway, aiding in finding points of interest, rest stops, or emergency services.</li>
<li><strong>Estimate Travel Times:</strong>  Calculate approximate travel times based on mile markers and known distances between destinations.</li>
<li><strong>Communicate with Emergency Services:</strong>  Provide precise locations in case of accidents or emergencies, ensuring swift and efficient response.</li>
<li><strong>Plan Rest Stops and Fueling:</strong>  Locate rest areas, gas stations, and other amenities along the route, ensuring comfort and convenience.</li>
<li><strong>Avoid Getting Lost:</strong>  Navigate unfamiliar areas with ease, especially in remote regions where GPS signals may be unreliable.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Types of Mile Marker Maps Available</strong></p>
<p>Several formats of Arizona mile marker maps cater to different needs and preferences:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Printed Maps:</strong> Traditional paper maps are widely available at gas stations, visitor centers, and online retailers. They provide a comprehensive overview of the entire state highway network.</li>
<li><strong>Online Maps:</strong> Websites like Google Maps, MapQuest, and specialized Arizona road atlas websites offer interactive mile marker maps, allowing for zoom, search, and route planning.</li>
<li><strong>Mobile Apps:</strong> Dedicated navigation apps like Waze and Google Maps integrate mile markers into their route guidance systems, offering real-time traffic updates and turn-by-turn directions.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Using Mile Marker Maps Effectively</strong></p>
<p>To maximize the benefits of mile marker maps, follow these guidelines:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Choose the Right Format:</strong>  Select the map format that best suits your travel style and needs, whether it&#8217;s a printed map for a long road trip or a mobile app for frequent route adjustments.</li>
<li><strong>Familiarize Yourself with the Map:</strong>  Before setting off, study the map to understand its layout, symbols, and legend, ensuring you can easily interpret the information.</li>
<li><strong>Mark Your Destination:</strong>  Highlight your destination on the map, noting the corresponding mile marker for easy reference during your journey.</li>
<li><strong>Check for Updates:</strong>  Mile marker maps are subject to change due to road construction or re-routing. Always refer to the most recent versions for accurate information.</li>
<li><strong>Use in Conjunction with GPS:</strong>  While mile marker maps are essential for understanding road networks, GPS devices can provide turn-by-turn directions and real-time traffic updates for a more comprehensive navigation experience.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>FAQs: Mile Marker Maps in Arizona</strong></p>
<p><strong>Q: Where can I find a comprehensive Arizona mile marker map?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Printed maps are available at gas stations, visitor centers, and online retailers like Amazon. Online resources like Google Maps, MapQuest, and specialized Arizona road atlas websites offer interactive mile marker maps.</p>
<p><strong>Q: Are mile markers consistent across all highways in Arizona?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Mile markers generally increase in numerical order as you travel further along a highway. However, some highways may have a different starting point for their mile marker system.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What information can I find on a mile marker map besides mile markers?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Mile marker maps often include points of interest like national parks, state parks, historical sites, rest areas, gas stations, and emergency services.</p>
<p><strong>Q: Are there any specific mile markers I should be aware of in Arizona?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Certain mile markers might mark the entrance to popular destinations like the Grand Canyon, Sedona, or Monument Valley. It&#8217;s advisable to research specific mile markers relevant to your planned route.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What should I do if I encounter a road closure or detour?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Consult the most recent version of your mile marker map or online resources for updates on road closures or detours. Road signs will also indicate alternative routes.</p>
<p><strong>Tips for Utilizing Mile Marker Maps in Arizona</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Plan Your Route:</strong>  Before embarking on your journey, carefully plan your route, noting the mile markers for key destinations, rest stops, and potential refueling points.</li>
<li><strong>Keep a Physical Map Handy:</strong>  Even with GPS navigation, a physical mile marker map serves as a valuable backup in case of electronic device failure or limited internet connectivity.</li>
<li><strong>Take Advantage of Rest Areas:</strong>  Utilize rest areas along the highway to take breaks, stretch your legs, and avoid fatigue, particularly on long drives.</li>
<li><strong>Be Prepared for Wildlife Encounters:</strong>  Arizona is home to various wildlife, including desert animals. Be cautious and aware of your surroundings, especially at dusk and dawn.</li>
<li><strong>Stay Informed About Weather Conditions:</strong>  Arizona&#8217;s weather can be unpredictable. Check weather forecasts and be prepared for potential changes in road conditions.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Conclusion: The Value of Mile Marker Maps in Arizona</strong></p>
<p>Mile marker maps are an invaluable tool for navigating Arizona&#8217;s vast and diverse roadways. By providing a clear and comprehensive visual guide, they empower travelers to plan their journeys effectively, locate points of interest, and ensure safe and enjoyable experiences. Whether you&#8217;re a seasoned traveler or a first-time visitor, embracing the use of mile marker maps enhances your understanding of Arizona&#8217;s road network and contributes to a successful and memorable journey. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://cdn.alltrips.com/maps/park/az_grand_canyon_village_max.jpg" alt="Navigating The Grand Canyon State: A Comprehensive Guide To Arizona’s " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="http://www.world-guides.com/images/grand_canyon/grand_canyon_map.jpg" alt="Navigating The Grand Canyon State: A Comprehensive Guide To Arizona’s " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="http://ridermagazine.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/web-Grand-Canyon-Ride.jpg" alt="Navigating The Grand Canyon State: A Comprehensive Guide To Arizona’s " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://i.pinimg.com/736x/8a/e3/ad/8ae3ad23cdc89734fc98c45d884830af.jpg" alt="Road Map of Arizona: the Grand Canyon State by North Star Mapping " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://www.americansouthwest.net/maps/grand-canyon-map.gif" alt="Map of Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-TDcP3u7P_gA/T_ZUfS1pbCI/AAAAAAAAB-I/YWsCpf8PYnM/s1600/Grand+Canyon+map.jpg" alt="Grand Canyon" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.westernriver.com/cdn-cgi/image/quality=60,/assets/img/maps/grand-canyon-upper-map.png" alt="Grand Canyon North America Map - Gisele Ermentrude" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://www.worldofmaps.net/fileadmin/_migrated/pics/map-grand-canyon.png" alt="Map of Arizona (Map of Grand Canyon National Park) : Worldofmaps.net " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"></p>
<h2 id="closure">Closure</h2>
<p>Thus, we hope this article has provided valuable insights into Navigating the Grand Canyon State: A Guide to Arizona Mile Marker Maps. We hope you find this article informative and beneficial. See you in our next article!</p><p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-grand-canyon-state-a-guide-to-arizona-mile-marker-maps-rbhkdc-pics/">Navigating The Grand Canyon State: A Guide To Arizona Mile Marker Maps</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-grand-canyon-state-a-guide-to-arizona-mile-marker-maps-rbhkdc-pics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
