<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>ozarks - Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks &amp; More</title>
	<atom:link href="/new-bjhlpy-tag/ozarks/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Discover Turkey’s cities, historical sites, and landscapes on Google Maps. Easily navigate through Istanbul, Cappadocia, Antalya, and beyond with interactive maps and street views.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:03:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Bull Shoals Lake: A Jewel Of The Ozarks</title>
		<link>/new-bjhlpy-bull-shoals-lake-a-jewel-of-the-ozarks-rbhkdc-pics/</link>
					<comments>/new-bjhlpy-bull-shoals-lake-a-jewel-of-the-ozarks-rbhkdc-pics/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[2025]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bull]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[jewel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lake]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ozarks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[shoals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://w1.geleleger.nl/bull-shoals-lake-a-jewel-of-the-ozarks/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bull Shoals Lake: A Jewel of the Ozarks Related Articles: Bull Shoals Lake: A Jewel [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-bull-shoals-lake-a-jewel-of-the-ozarks-rbhkdc-pics/">Bull Shoals Lake: A Jewel Of The Ozarks</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bull Shoals Lake: A Jewel of the Ozarks</p>
<h2 id="related-articles:-bull-shoals-lake:-a-jewel-of-the-ozarks">Related Articles: Bull Shoals Lake: A Jewel of the Ozarks</h2>
<h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2>
<p>With great pleasure, we will explore the intriguing topic related to Bull Shoals Lake: A Jewel of the Ozarks. Let&#8217;s weave interesting information and offer fresh perspectives to the readers.</p>
<div id="toc">
<h2>Table of Content</h2>
<ul>
<li><a href="#related-articles:-bull-shoals-lake:-a-jewel-of-the-ozarks">1 Related Articles: Bull Shoals Lake: A Jewel of the Ozarks</a></li>
<li><a href="#introduction">2 Introduction</a></li>
<li><a href="#bull-shoals-lake:-a-jewel-of-the-ozarks">3 Bull Shoals Lake: A Jewel of the Ozarks</a></li>
<li><a href="#closure">4 Closure</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2 id="bull-shoals-lake:-a-jewel-of-the-ozarks">Bull Shoals Lake: A Jewel of the Ozarks</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://www.houseboating.org/media/Bull-Shoals-Lake-Houseboat-Rentals-Media-5-800x600.jpg" alt="Bull Shoals Lake - Houseboat Photos  Pictures" /></p>
<p>Bull Shoals Lake, a sprawling reservoir nestled in the Ozark Mountains of northern Arkansas and southern Missouri, is a captivating destination for outdoor enthusiasts, anglers, and nature lovers alike. Formed by the construction of Bull Shoals Dam in the 1950s, the lake boasts over 700 miles of shoreline, offering a vast expanse of pristine waters and scenic vistas.</p>
<p><strong>A Symphony of Natural Beauty:</strong></p>
<p>The lake&#8217;s beauty is undeniable. Its emerald-green waters reflect the surrounding Ozark Mountains, creating a picturesque panorama. The shoreline is dotted with rocky bluffs, forested islands, and secluded coves, each offering a unique perspective on the lake&#8217;s charm. The presence of diverse wildlife, including bald eagles, osprey, and various fish species, further enriches the natural tapestry of the region.</p>
<p><strong>A Paradise for Anglers:</strong></p>
<p>Bull Shoals Lake is renowned for its exceptional fishing opportunities. The lake&#8217;s deep waters and abundant aquatic life create a haven for a wide variety of fish, including bass, crappie, walleye, catfish, and trout. Anglers can enjoy casting their lines from the shore, renting a boat, or embarking on guided fishing trips, all offering the chance to reel in a prized catch.</p>
<p><strong>Exploring the Lake&#8217;s Depths:</strong></p>
<p>Beyond fishing, Bull Shoals Lake offers a plethora of water-based activities. Boaters can cruise across the lake, explore its numerous coves and inlets, or anchor in secluded spots for a relaxing picnic. Kayaking and canoeing provide a more intimate experience, allowing visitors to navigate through serene waterways and observe the lake&#8217;s natural beauty up close.</p>
<p><strong>Land-Based Adventures:</strong></p>
<p>The surrounding area offers a wealth of land-based activities as well. Hiking trails wind through the Ozark Mountains, offering panoramic views of the lake and its surroundings. The region is also home to numerous state parks, offering opportunities for camping, picnicking, and exploring the natural beauty of the Ozarks.</p>
<p><strong>Historical Significance:</strong></p>
<p>Bull Shoals Lake holds historical significance as a vital source of hydroelectric power for the region. The dam that created the lake remains a testament to engineering ingenuity and the transformative power of human endeavor. Visitors can learn about the lake&#8217;s history and the dam&#8217;s construction at the nearby Bull Shoals Dam Visitor Center.</p>
<p><strong>Economic Impact:</strong></p>
<p>The lake plays a crucial role in the local economy, attracting tourists and supporting businesses related to recreation, tourism, and hospitality. The lake&#8217;s popularity has led to the development of numerous marinas, resorts, restaurants, and shops, creating a thriving community centered around its unique appeal.</p>
<p><strong>Conservation and Preservation:</strong></p>
<p>The preservation of Bull Shoals Lake&#8217;s natural beauty and ecological integrity is paramount. The lake is managed by the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, which implements regulations to ensure the sustainability of its resources and the health of its ecosystem.</p>
<p><strong>Frequently Asked Questions</strong></p>
<p><strong>Q: When is the best time to visit Bull Shoals Lake?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> The best time to visit Bull Shoals Lake depends on individual preferences. Spring and fall offer mild temperatures and vibrant foliage, while summer provides warm weather ideal for swimming and boating.</p>
<p><strong>Q: Are there any fees to access the lake?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Access to the lake is generally free, but some facilities and activities may require fees. For example, boat ramps and campgrounds may charge usage fees.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What are the fishing regulations for Bull Shoals Lake?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Fishing regulations are enforced by the Arkansas Game and Fish Commission. Anglers must obtain a fishing license and adhere to specific size and bag limits for various fish species.</p>
<p><strong>Q: Are there any campgrounds near Bull Shoals Lake?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Yes, there are numerous campgrounds located around the lake, offering various amenities and options for camping. Some campgrounds are operated by the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, while others are privately owned.</p>
<p><strong>Q: Are there any boat rentals available on the lake?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Yes, several marinas and boat rental companies operate on the lake, offering a variety of watercraft for rent, including pontoon boats, fishing boats, and kayaks.</p>
<p><strong>Tips for Visiting Bull Shoals Lake:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Plan your trip in advance:</strong> Research the available activities, accommodations, and attractions to make the most of your visit.</li>
<li><strong>Bring appropriate gear:</strong> Depending on your activities, pack clothing, footwear, sunscreen, and other essentials.</li>
<li><strong>Be aware of weather conditions:</strong> The weather in the Ozarks can be unpredictable, so check forecasts and be prepared for changing conditions.</li>
<li><strong>Respect the environment:</strong> Dispose of trash properly, avoid disturbing wildlife, and adhere to regulations to protect the lake&#8217;s natural beauty.</li>
<li><strong>Consider visiting during off-peak seasons:</strong> To avoid crowds and enjoy a more peaceful experience, consider visiting during the shoulder seasons (spring and fall).</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Conclusion:</strong></p>
<p>Bull Shoals Lake stands as a testament to the natural beauty and recreational opportunities found in the Ozarks. Its sprawling waters, picturesque surroundings, and diverse activities offer an unforgettable experience for visitors of all ages. Whether seeking a serene escape, an adrenaline-pumping adventure, or simply a chance to connect with nature, Bull Shoals Lake provides a sanctuary for relaxation, exploration, and unforgettable memories. The lake&#8217;s importance as a source of recreation, economic vitality, and ecological significance underscores its enduring appeal and its role as a treasured destination for generations to come. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/sE7Uchvrlp4/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="Exploring the Beauty of Bull Shoals Lake in the Ozarks of Southern MO " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://static.visionamp.org/rubix/20160526/800_09dbee156d4ab1ff45635d3f0b9f57374c20f9ae.jpg" alt="Things to do at Bull Shoals Lake - Bull Shoals Lake - Explore the Ozarks" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5228c637e4b0001f2a37eb47/1424645949721-ZKPEBTL6H3STYFRYPUHR/Bull+Shoals+Lake+shoreling.jpg" alt="The Bull Shoals Lake Shoreline — Sierra Ozark Corporation" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/4rqufffHIWI/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="Exploring the Beauty of Bull Shoals Lake in the Ozarks of Missouri " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://www.cardcow.com/images/set69/card00030_fr.jpg" alt="Beautiful Bull Shoals Lake In The Ozarks Lake Ozark, MO" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://static.visionamp.org/rubix/20160526/800_43bd39b06ceda498513676d2f20ff393199b5e2c.jpg" alt="Things to do at Bull Shoals Lake - Bull Shoals Lake - Explore the Ozarks" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="http://diamondcityarkansas.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/1974-marina-shot.jpg" alt="Diamond City, Arkansas – The Jewel of Bull Shoals Lake" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://workingwellresources.files.wordpress.com/2013/02/dsc03274.jpg" alt="Plan a Getaway to Missouri’s Bull Shoals Lake in the Ozarks  Working " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"></p>
<h2 id="closure">Closure</h2>
<p>Thus, we hope this article has provided valuable insights into Bull Shoals Lake: A Jewel of the Ozarks. We appreciate your attention to our article. See you in our next article!</p><p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-bull-shoals-lake-a-jewel-of-the-ozarks-rbhkdc-pics/">Bull Shoals Lake: A Jewel Of The Ozarks</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/new-bjhlpy-bull-shoals-lake-a-jewel-of-the-ozarks-rbhkdc-pics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Navigating The Waters Of Adventure: A Comprehensive Guide To The Map Of Lake Of The Ozarks, Missouri</title>
		<link>/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-waters-of-adventure-a-comprehensive-guide-to-the-map-of-lake-of-the-ozarks-missouri-rbhkdc-pics/</link>
					<comments>/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-waters-of-adventure-a-comprehensive-guide-to-the-map-of-lake-of-the-ozarks-missouri-rbhkdc-pics/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[2025]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[adventure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[comprehensive]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[guide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lake]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[map]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[missouri]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[navigating]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ozarks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[to]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[waters]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://w1.geleleger.nl/navigating-the-waters-of-adventure-a-comprehensive-guide-to-the-map-of-lake-of-the-ozarks-missouri/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Navigating the Waters of Adventure: A Comprehensive Guide to the Map of Lake of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-waters-of-adventure-a-comprehensive-guide-to-the-map-of-lake-of-the-ozarks-missouri-rbhkdc-pics/">Navigating The Waters Of Adventure: A Comprehensive Guide To The Map Of Lake Of The Ozarks, Missouri</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Navigating the Waters of Adventure: A Comprehensive Guide to the Map of Lake of the Ozarks, Missouri</p>
<h2 id="related-articles:-navigating-the-waters-of-adventure:-a-comprehensive-guide-to-the-map-of-lake-of-the-ozarks,-missouri">Related Articles: Navigating the Waters of Adventure: A Comprehensive Guide to the Map of Lake of the Ozarks, Missouri</h2>
<h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2>
<p>In this auspicious occasion, we are delighted to delve into the intriguing topic related to Navigating the Waters of Adventure: A Comprehensive Guide to the Map of Lake of the Ozarks, Missouri. Let&#8217;s weave interesting information and offer fresh perspectives to the readers.</p>
<div id="toc">
<h2>Table of Content</h2>
<ul>
<li><a href="#related-articles:-navigating-the-waters-of-adventure:-a-comprehensive-guide-to-the-map-of-lake-of-the-ozarks,-missouri">1 Related Articles: Navigating the Waters of Adventure: A Comprehensive Guide to the Map of Lake of the Ozarks, Missouri</a></li>
<li><a href="#introduction">2 Introduction</a></li>
<li><a href="#navigating-the-waters-of-adventure:-a-comprehensive-guide-to-the-map-of-lake-of-the-ozarks,-missouri">3 Navigating the Waters of Adventure: A Comprehensive Guide to the Map of Lake of the Ozarks, Missouri</a></li>
<li><a href="#closure">4 Closure</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2 id="navigating-the-waters-of-adventure:-a-comprehensive-guide-to-the-map-of-lake-of-the-ozarks,-missouri">Navigating the Waters of Adventure: A Comprehensive Guide to the Map of Lake of the Ozarks, Missouri</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://www.lakeozarkrealty.com/img/lake%20of%20the%20ozarks%20map.jpeg" alt="Navigating The Waters Of Success: A Comprehensive Guide To Lake Of The " /></p>
<p>The Lake of the Ozarks, a sprawling expanse of water nestled in the heart of Missouri, is a destination renowned for its diverse offerings. From tranquil coves to bustling marinas, from pristine beaches to towering bluffs, this vast reservoir offers a myriad of experiences for visitors. Understanding the intricacies of the Lake of the Ozarks map is crucial for unlocking the full potential of this captivating destination.</p>
<p><strong>The Geography of a Man-Made Wonder:</strong></p>
<p>The Lake of the Ozarks was formed in 1931 with the construction of the Bagnell Dam on the Osage River. This feat of engineering created a 130-mile-long, 1,150-mile-shoreline reservoir, transforming the landscape and creating a unique ecosystem. The map of Lake of the Ozarks reflects this artificial origin, showcasing a complex network of coves, inlets, and arms, each with its distinct character.</p>
<p><strong>A Map for Every Adventure:</strong></p>
<p>The Lake of the Ozarks map is not a singular entity. It exists in various forms, catering to different needs and interests. The most basic maps, often found in tourist brochures or online, provide a general overview of the lake&#8217;s main areas, highlighting major landmarks, towns, and attractions. More detailed maps, available from local businesses or specialized mapping websites, delve deeper, illustrating specific coves, inlets, and points of interest.</p>
<p>For boaters, navigating the vastness of the lake requires a specialized map, often in nautical chart form. These charts display water depths, channel markers, and navigational hazards, ensuring safe and efficient passage. Anglers, too, rely on specific maps detailing fishing hotspots, known for specific species and fishing techniques.</p>
<p><strong>Unveiling the Hidden Treasures:</strong></p>
<p>The Lake of the Ozarks map serves as a key to unlocking the diverse experiences the region offers. It guides visitors to:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Scenic Drives:</strong> The map reveals winding roads that hug the shoreline, offering breathtaking vistas of the lake and its surrounding hills.</li>
<li><strong>Charming Towns:</strong> From the vibrant city of Osage Beach to the quaint village of Lake Ozark, the map leads to unique communities, each with its own character and attractions.</li>
<li><strong>Outdoor Adventures:</strong> Whether it&#8217;s hiking through the Ozark hills, exploring nature trails, or enjoying water sports, the map guides visitors to diverse outdoor recreational areas.</li>
<li><strong>Historical Sites:</strong> The map unveils historic landmarks, remnants of the region&#8217;s rich past, reminding visitors of the area&#8217;s cultural heritage.</li>
<li><strong>Culinary Delights:</strong> From fine dining restaurants to casual cafes, the map directs visitors to local eateries serving fresh, regional cuisine.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Beyond the Basics:</strong></p>
<p>Beyond the physical map, digital resources offer a wealth of information and interactivity. Online mapping tools, like Google Maps and other specialized platforms, provide real-time traffic updates, location-based services, and interactive features. These tools allow visitors to plan their itineraries, discover hidden gems, and navigate with ease.</p>
<p><strong>FAQs about the Lake of the Ozarks Map:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Q: What are the best resources for obtaining detailed maps of the Lake of the Ozarks?</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>A: Local marinas, tourism bureaus, and outdoor recreation stores are excellent sources for detailed maps. Specialized mapping websites, such as those dedicated to boating or fishing, also provide comprehensive maps.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Q: Are there specific maps for navigating the lake by boat?</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>A: Yes, nautical charts are essential for boating on the Lake of the Ozarks. These charts detail water depths, channel markers, and navigational hazards, crucial for safe passage.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Q: What is the best way to find fishing hotspots on the Lake of the Ozarks map?</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>A: Specialized fishing maps, often available at bait shops and tackle stores, highlight known fishing spots, indicating species and preferred fishing techniques.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Q: How can I use the map to plan a scenic drive around the lake?</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>A: Use the map to identify roads that hug the shoreline, offering panoramic views. Look for designated scenic overlooks and points of interest along the route.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Q: Are there any apps or online tools that enhance the use of the Lake of the Ozarks map?</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>A: Yes, online mapping tools like Google Maps and specialized platforms offer real-time traffic updates, location-based services, and interactive features, enhancing the overall experience.</p>
<p><strong>Tips for Using the Lake of the Ozarks Map Effectively:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Plan Ahead:</strong> Before embarking on any adventure, study the map and familiarize yourself with the area.</li>
<li><strong>Consider Your Interests:</strong> Choose a map that caters to your specific needs, whether it&#8217;s for boating, fishing, or exploring the surrounding areas.</li>
<li><strong>Utilize Digital Resources:</strong> Explore online mapping tools to enhance your navigation and discovery experience.</li>
<li><strong>Embrace the Unexpected:</strong> Allow the map to guide you to unexpected discoveries, hidden gems, and new adventures.</li>
<li><strong>Respect the Environment:</strong>  Be mindful of the natural beauty of the area and practice responsible tourism.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Conclusion:</strong></p>
<p>The map of Lake of the Ozarks is more than just a guide; it&#8217;s a key to unlocking the full potential of this captivating destination. Whether navigating the waters by boat, exploring the scenic highways, or discovering hidden treasures, the map serves as a vital tool for unlocking the diverse experiences offered by this Missouri gem. By understanding the intricacies of the map and utilizing its various forms, visitors can embark on a journey of discovery, adventure, and lasting memories. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="http://www.gpsnauticalcharts.com/static_html/nautical_charts_app/nautical_chart_images/US_MO_00729600.jpg" alt="Lake of the Ozarks Fishing Map  Nautical Charts App" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://ke-courses-production.s3.amazonaws.com/asset_files/production/1402/attachments/original/navigation_map.jpg?1503937870" alt="Navigating The Waters Of Development: A Comprehensive Guide To River " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/2b/b9/2e/2bb92e3f5104c10838413f21f452abee.jpg" alt="Boundary Waters Canoe Area: Paddling Into The Wild  Boundary waters " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://fish-and-hunt.net/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/Lake-Cumberland-Map.jpg" alt="Detailed Map Of Lake Cumberland" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://www.boatsetter.com/boating-resources/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/navigating-rough-waters.jpg" alt="3 Boating Tips on Navigating Rough Waters  Boatsetter" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://tdalloutdoors.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/07/BWCA-map-REDONE.jpg" alt="Boundary Waters Canoe Area Maps - Planning A Canoe Route" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://wildwater.net/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/map_rides_only_2.jpg" alt="Rapids Water Park Map - Map Of Stoney Lake" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://mir-s3-cdn-cf.behance.net/project_modules/max_1200/2bba5730324177.561dbe62047e4.png" alt="Waterpark Brochure on Behance" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"></p>
<h2 id="closure">Closure</h2>
<p>Thus, we hope this article has provided valuable insights into Navigating the Waters of Adventure: A Comprehensive Guide to the Map of Lake of the Ozarks, Missouri. We appreciate your attention to our article. See you in our next article!</p><p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-waters-of-adventure-a-comprehensive-guide-to-the-map-of-lake-of-the-ozarks-missouri-rbhkdc-pics/">Navigating The Waters Of Adventure: A Comprehensive Guide To The Map Of Lake Of The Ozarks, Missouri</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-waters-of-adventure-a-comprehensive-guide-to-the-map-of-lake-of-the-ozarks-missouri-rbhkdc-pics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
