<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>risks - Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks &amp; More</title>
	<atom:link href="/new-bjhlpy-tag/risks/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Discover Turkey’s cities, historical sites, and landscapes on Google Maps. Easily navigate through Istanbul, Cappadocia, Antalya, and beyond with interactive maps and street views.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:36:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Navigating The Risks: Understanding West Virginia&#8217;s Flood Maps</title>
		<link>/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-risks-understanding-west-virginias-flood-maps-rbhkdc-pics/</link>
					<comments>/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-risks-understanding-west-virginias-flood-maps-rbhkdc-pics/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[2025]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[flood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[maps]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[navigating]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[risks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[understanding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virginias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[west]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://w1.geleleger.nl/navigating-the-risks-understanding-west-virginias-flood-maps/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Navigating the Risks: Understanding West Virginia&#8217;s Flood Maps Related Articles: Navigating the Risks: Understanding West [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-risks-understanding-west-virginias-flood-maps-rbhkdc-pics/">Navigating The Risks: Understanding West Virginia’s Flood Maps</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Navigating the Risks: Understanding West Virginia&#8217;s Flood Maps</p>
<h2 id="related-articles:-navigating-the-risks:-understanding-west-virginia's-flood-maps">Related Articles: Navigating the Risks: Understanding West Virginia&#8217;s Flood Maps</h2>
<h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2>
<p>With great pleasure, we will explore the intriguing topic related to Navigating the Risks: Understanding West Virginia&#8217;s Flood Maps. Let&#8217;s weave interesting information and offer fresh perspectives to the readers.</p>
<div id="toc">
<h2>Table of Content</h2>
<ul>
<li><a href="#related-articles:-navigating-the-risks:-understanding-west-virginia's-flood-maps">1 Related Articles: Navigating the Risks: Understanding West Virginia&#8217;s Flood Maps</a></li>
<li><a href="#introduction">2 Introduction</a></li>
<li><a href="#navigating-the-risks:-understanding-west-virginia's-flood-maps">3 Navigating the Risks: Understanding West Virginia&#8217;s Flood Maps</a></li>
<li><a href="#closure">4 Closure</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2 id="navigating-the-risks:-understanding-west-virginia's-flood-maps">Navigating the Risks: Understanding West Virginia&#8217;s Flood Maps</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://gray-wdtv-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/xy0vV-wFewnEO3y6JdRwvLEvDgI=/1200x675/smart/filters:quality(85)/cloudfront-us-east-1.images.arcpublishing.com/gray/KGSNE4NSUFE6DHHJ6LNU72FKTY.png" alt="West Virginia launches flood tool to help assess flood risk" /></p>
<p>West Virginia, known for its rolling hills and verdant landscapes, also faces the persistent threat of flooding. The state&#8217;s topography, characterized by steep slopes and numerous rivers and streams, makes it particularly susceptible to heavy rainfall and flash flooding. To mitigate these risks, the Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA) has developed comprehensive flood maps for West Virginia, providing crucial information for residents, businesses, and policymakers. </p>
<p><strong>The Significance of Flood Maps</strong></p>
<p>Flood maps are indispensable tools for understanding and managing flood risks. They serve as visual representations of areas prone to flooding, delineating flood zones and their associated risk levels. This information is vital for:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>Informed Decision-Making:</strong> Flood maps empower individuals and communities to make informed decisions regarding land use, development, and infrastructure planning. By identifying flood-prone areas, they guide responsible development, minimizing the risk of future flood damage and ensuring the safety of residents and property.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Insurance Premiums and Coverage:</strong> Flood maps are directly linked to flood insurance policies. Properties located in designated flood zones are typically required to purchase flood insurance, reflecting the higher risk of flood damage. This requirement ensures financial protection for homeowners and businesses in the event of a flood.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Emergency Response and Planning:</strong> Flood maps facilitate effective emergency response and preparedness. By identifying potential flood zones, emergency responders can anticipate flood risks, plan evacuation routes, and allocate resources efficiently during flood events.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Community Resilience:</strong> Flood maps contribute to building community resilience by fostering awareness, promoting preparedness, and encouraging proactive measures to mitigate flood risks. By understanding the potential impacts of flooding, communities can implement preventive measures, such as elevating structures, improving drainage systems, and enacting stricter building codes.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Understanding the Flood Zones</strong></p>
<p>FEMA&#8217;s flood maps categorize areas into different flood zones, each representing a distinct level of flood risk:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>Special Flood Hazard Areas (SFHAs):</strong> These zones are considered to be at high risk of flooding. Properties within SFHAs are typically required to purchase flood insurance.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Areas of Minimal Flood Risk:</strong> These zones are generally considered to be at low risk of flooding, although they may still be subject to occasional minor flooding events.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Undetermined Flood Risk Areas:</strong> These zones have not yet been fully evaluated for flood risk.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Accessing and Interpreting Flood Maps</strong></p>
<p>FEMA&#8217;s flood maps are readily available online through the agency&#8217;s website, FloodSmart.gov. The maps can be viewed interactively, allowing users to zoom in on specific areas and identify flood zones. </p>
<p><strong>Interpreting the maps requires understanding the following key elements:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>Flood Zone Designations:</strong> The maps clearly indicate the various flood zones, using distinct colors or symbols to represent different risk levels.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Base Flood Elevation (BFE):</strong> This refers to the elevation to which floodwaters are expected to rise during a 100-year flood event, a flood with a 1% chance of occurring in any given year.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Floodway:</strong> This is the area within a floodplain that is required to carry floodwaters. Development within floodways is often restricted to minimize the risk of obstructing flood flows.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Beyond the Maps: Additional Resources and Considerations</strong></p>
<p>While flood maps provide invaluable information, they are not static. Factors such as climate change, urbanization, and changes in land use can influence flood risks. It is crucial to consider these factors and consult additional resources for a comprehensive understanding of flood risks:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>Local Floodplain Management Plans:</strong> These plans provide detailed information on flood risks and mitigation strategies specific to individual communities.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>National Weather Service (NWS) Flood Forecasts:</strong> The NWS provides real-time flood forecasts and warnings, offering valuable information during periods of heavy rainfall or potential flood events.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Local Emergency Management Agencies:</strong> These agencies can provide information on flood preparedness, evacuation routes, and other emergency measures.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Frequently Asked Questions</strong></p>
<p><strong>Q: What is a 100-year flood?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> A 100-year flood refers to a flood event with a 1% chance of occurring in any given year. It is important to note that this does not mean that such a flood will occur only once every 100 years. It is possible to experience multiple 100-year flood events within a shorter period.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What does it mean if my property is in a flood zone?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> If your property is located within a Special Flood Hazard Area (SFHA), you are typically required to purchase flood insurance. This requirement is designed to protect property owners from financial losses in the event of a flood.</p>
<p><strong>Q: Can I rebuild my property in a flood zone?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Building codes and regulations vary depending on the specific flood zone and local ordinances. In some cases, rebuilding in a flood zone may require specific flood mitigation measures, such as elevating the structure above the base flood elevation.</p>
<p><strong>Q: How often are flood maps updated?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> FEMA updates its flood maps periodically, typically every five to ten years. However, the frequency of updates may vary depending on local conditions and the availability of new data.</p>
<p><strong>Tips for Mitigating Flood Risks</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p><strong>Elevate Structures:</strong> Elevating structures above the base flood elevation can significantly reduce the risk of flood damage.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Install Flood Barriers:</strong> Installing flood barriers, such as sandbags or flood walls, can help protect properties from rising floodwaters.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Improve Drainage:</strong> Ensuring proper drainage around your property can prevent water from pooling and infiltrating your home.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Maintain Vegetation:</strong> Trees and other vegetation can help absorb rainwater and reduce the risk of flooding.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Develop a Flood Emergency Plan:</strong> Having a plan in place for evacuation, securing belongings, and contacting emergency services can minimize the impact of a flood event.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>
<p>West Virginia&#8217;s flood maps are essential tools for understanding and managing flood risks. By providing clear and accessible information on flood zones and risk levels, these maps empower individuals, businesses, and communities to make informed decisions, plan effectively, and build resilience against the threat of flooding. By utilizing these resources and implementing mitigation measures, West Virginians can better prepare for and navigate the challenges posed by flood events, protecting their properties and ensuring the safety of their communities. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="http://www.mapwv.gov/img/flooding2.fw.png" alt="MapWV.gov" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/proxy/-FWggqjF7Axu4BQug-MDft4UNkDMzTsbe_2xkggBD4w18WYPqt3ZajB0aGEmp78feO_efXalUxYKF6WF06fUNnhpJ6WQ-ioYLLXpQNjy0w=s0-d" alt="Flooding In West Virginia Map - Maping Resources" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="http://www.nrcc.cornell.edu/services/blog/2016/06/24/20160624_RLXradar.jpg" alt="Flooding In West Virginia Map - Maping Resources" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://gis.fema.gov/maps/disaster/dec_1558.png" alt="West Virginia Severe Storms, Flooding And Landslides (DR-1558-WV " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://gis.fema.gov/maps/disaster/dec_4210.png" alt="Flooding In West Virginia Map - Maping Resources" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="http://wvgis.wvu.edu/data/statusgraphics/FLOOD_HAZARD/status_FloodMapping20130308.png" alt="www.wvgis.wvu.edu - /data/statusGraphics/FLOOD_HAZARD/" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.weather.gov/images/safety/wv-5-1.jpg" alt="Flooding In West Virginia Map – Map VectorCampus Map" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://www.climate.gov/sites/default/files/1000yr24hrRainfall_nwebb.jpg" alt="&#39;Thousand-year&#39; downpour led to deadly West Virginia floods  NOAA " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"></p>
<h2 id="closure">Closure</h2>
<p>Thus, we hope this article has provided valuable insights into Navigating the Risks: Understanding West Virginia&#8217;s Flood Maps. We thank you for taking the time to read this article. See you in our next article!</p><p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-risks-understanding-west-virginias-flood-maps-rbhkdc-pics/">Navigating The Risks: Understanding West Virginia’s Flood Maps</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/new-bjhlpy-navigating-the-risks-understanding-west-virginias-flood-maps-rbhkdc-pics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mapping The Scars: Understanding Flood Risks In West Virginia</title>
		<link>/new-bjhlpy-mapping-the-scars-understanding-flood-risks-in-west-virginia-rbhkdc-pics/</link>
					<comments>/new-bjhlpy-mapping-the-scars-understanding-flood-risks-in-west-virginia-rbhkdc-pics/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 22:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[2025]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[flood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mapping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[risks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[scars]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[understanding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[virginia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[west]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://w1.geleleger.nl/mapping-the-scars-understanding-flood-risks-in-west-virginia/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mapping the Scars: Understanding Flood Risks in West Virginia Related Articles: Mapping the Scars: Understanding [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-mapping-the-scars-understanding-flood-risks-in-west-virginia-rbhkdc-pics/">Mapping The Scars: Understanding Flood Risks In West Virginia</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mapping the Scars: Understanding Flood Risks in West Virginia</p>
<h2 id="related-articles:-mapping-the-scars:-understanding-flood-risks-in-west-virginia">Related Articles: Mapping the Scars: Understanding Flood Risks in West Virginia</h2>
<h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2>
<p>In this auspicious occasion, we are delighted to delve into the intriguing topic related to Mapping the Scars: Understanding Flood Risks in West Virginia. Let&#8217;s weave interesting information and offer fresh perspectives to the readers.</p>
<div id="toc">
<h2>Table of Content</h2>
<ul>
<li><a href="#related-articles:-mapping-the-scars:-understanding-flood-risks-in-west-virginia">1 Related Articles: Mapping the Scars: Understanding Flood Risks in West Virginia</a></li>
<li><a href="#introduction">2 Introduction</a></li>
<li><a href="#mapping-the-scars:-understanding-flood-risks-in-west-virginia">3 Mapping the Scars: Understanding Flood Risks in West Virginia</a></li>
<li><a href="#closure">4 Closure</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2 id="mapping-the-scars:-understanding-flood-risks-in-west-virginia">Mapping the Scars: Understanding Flood Risks in West Virginia</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://gray-wdtv-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/xy0vV-wFewnEO3y6JdRwvLEvDgI=/1200x675/smart/filters:quality(85)/cloudfront-us-east-1.images.arcpublishing.com/gray/KGSNE4NSUFE6DHHJ6LNU72FKTY.png" alt="West Virginia launches flood tool to help assess flood risk" /></p>
<p>West Virginia, a state renowned for its rugged beauty and Appalachian heritage, faces a persistent threat: flooding. The state&#8217;s mountainous terrain, dense forests, and often-intense rainfall create a perfect storm for devastating floods, leaving communities vulnerable and infrastructure in ruins. Understanding the geography of flooding in West Virginia is crucial for mitigating its impact, fostering preparedness, and informing future development.</p>
<p><strong>A State Shaped by Water:</strong></p>
<p>West Virginia&#8217;s topography plays a pivotal role in its susceptibility to flooding. Its numerous rivers, streams, and tributaries, carving their way through the Appalachian Mountains, act as natural conduits for water flow. The steep slopes and narrow valleys amplify the speed and volume of water rushing downstream, quickly transforming gentle streams into raging torrents. This rapid flow exacerbates the impact of rainfall, especially during intense storms or periods of snowmelt.</p>
<p><strong>Mapping the Flood Zones:</strong></p>
<p>Maps serve as invaluable tools for visualizing flood risk, revealing the areas most vulnerable to inundation. These maps, often created by government agencies like the Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), utilize data on historical flood events, elevation, and river flow to identify floodplains and hazard zones. </p>
<p><strong>Understanding the Color Codes:</strong></p>
<p>Flood hazard maps typically use color coding to delineate different levels of flood risk. For instance, areas shaded in blue may represent a 100-year floodplain, signifying a 1% chance of flooding in any given year. Areas in darker shades, like red or purple, indicate higher flood risks, suggesting a greater probability of inundation.</p>
<p><strong>The Importance of Flood Maps:</strong></p>
<p>Flood maps serve several critical functions:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Risk Assessment:</strong> Maps provide a visual representation of flood risk, allowing individuals, communities, and policymakers to understand the potential dangers and prioritize mitigation efforts.</li>
<li><strong>Development Planning:</strong> By identifying flood-prone areas, maps guide responsible land use planning, preventing the construction of critical infrastructure or residential developments in high-risk zones.</li>
<li><strong>Insurance and Financing:</strong> Flood maps inform insurance premiums and loan eligibility, enabling individuals and businesses to assess their financial exposure to flooding.</li>
<li><strong>Emergency Response:</strong> Maps assist emergency responders in identifying vulnerable areas, optimizing evacuation routes, and allocating resources during flood events.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Beyond the Maps: A Multifaceted Approach to Flood Mitigation:</strong></p>
<p>While maps provide valuable insights, they are just one tool in a multifaceted approach to flood mitigation. Effective flood management requires a collaborative effort involving:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Engineering Solutions:</strong> Implementing flood control structures like dams, levees, and channels can reduce the impact of flooding by managing water flow and diverting excess water.</li>
<li><strong>Land Use Planning:</strong> Restricting development in floodplains and promoting natural floodplains can minimize flood damage and enhance the natural resilience of ecosystems.</li>
<li><strong>Early Warning Systems:</strong> Advanced weather forecasting and early warning systems allow communities to prepare for impending floods, enabling timely evacuations and reducing loss of life.</li>
<li><strong>Community Education and Preparedness:</strong> Educating residents about flood risks, promoting flood insurance, and fostering community-based preparedness plans are crucial for minimizing the impact of flooding.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>FAQs About Flood Maps in West Virginia:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Q: How can I find flood maps for my area in West Virginia?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> You can access flood maps through the Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA) website, the West Virginia Department of Homeland Security, and local county and municipal government websites.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What does a 100-year floodplain mean?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> A 100-year floodplain signifies a 1% chance of flooding in any given year. It does not mean that flooding will occur only once every 100 years, but rather that there is a 1% probability of flooding in any given year.</p>
<p><strong>Q: Are flood maps updated regularly?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Flood maps are periodically updated based on new data, including historical flood events, climate change projections, and changes in land use. It is essential to consult the most recent versions of the maps for accurate information.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What are the consequences of building in a floodplain?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Building in a floodplain poses significant risks, including potential property damage, financial losses, and even loss of life. It is crucial to consider the potential impact of flooding before making any development decisions.</p>
<p><strong>Tips for Using Flood Maps in West Virginia:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Understand your risk:</strong> Identify your property&#8217;s location relative to floodplains and hazard zones.</li>
<li><strong>Consult with local officials:</strong> Seek guidance from local government agencies regarding flood risks and regulations.</li>
<li><strong>Consider flood insurance:</strong> Obtain flood insurance if your property is located in a flood-prone area.</li>
<li><strong>Prepare for emergencies:</strong> Develop a family emergency plan, including evacuation routes and communication protocols.</li>
<li><strong>Stay informed about weather forecasts:</strong> Monitor weather reports and heed warnings about potential flooding.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Conclusion:</strong></p>
<p>Flood maps are essential tools for understanding and mitigating flood risks in West Virginia. By visualizing flood-prone areas, these maps empower individuals, communities, and policymakers to make informed decisions, prioritize development, and protect lives and property. While maps are critical for assessing flood risk, they are just one component of a multifaceted approach to flood management. By integrating engineering solutions, land use planning, early warning systems, and community preparedness, West Virginia can work towards a future where flooding is not a devastating force but a manageable risk. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="http://wvgis.wvu.edu/data/statusgraphics/FLOOD_HAZARD/status_FloodMapping20130308.png" alt="www.wvgis.wvu.edu - /data/statusGraphics/FLOOD_HAZARD/" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://www.climate.gov/sites/default/files/1000yr24hrRainfall_nwebb.jpg" alt="&#39;Thousand-year&#39; downpour led to deadly West Virginia floods  NOAA " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://gis.fema.gov/maps/disaster/dec_1558.png" alt="West Virginia Severe Storms, Flooding And Landslides (DR-1558-WV " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://venngage-wordpress-gallery.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/2016/09/the-us-flood-risk-map.png" alt="The Us Flood Risk Map" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://www.weather.gov/images/safety/wv-5-1.jpg" alt="Flooding In West Virginia Map - Map" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://www.esa.int/var/esa/storage/images/esa_multimedia/images/2006/05/flood_risk_map_of_badger/9636120-3-eng-GB/Flood_risk_map_of_Badger.jpg" alt="Flood Risk Map" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/nCeXChN1T0I/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="Flood Risk Assessment and Mapping using ArcGIS - YouTube" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://www.frontiersin.org/files/Articles/540869/feart-08-00304-HTML/image_m/feart-08-00304-g007.jpg" alt="Frontiers  Community Mapping Supports Comprehensive Urban Flood " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"></p>
<h2 id="closure">Closure</h2>
<p>Thus, we hope this article has provided valuable insights into Mapping the Scars: Understanding Flood Risks in West Virginia. We thank you for taking the time to read this article. See you in our next article!</p><p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-mapping-the-scars-understanding-flood-risks-in-west-virginia-rbhkdc-pics/">Mapping The Scars: Understanding Flood Risks In West Virginia</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/new-bjhlpy-mapping-the-scars-understanding-flood-risks-in-west-virginia-rbhkdc-pics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
