<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>rising - Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks &amp; More</title>
	<atom:link href="/new-bjhlpy-tag/rising/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Discover Turkey’s cities, historical sites, and landscapes on Google Maps. Easily navigate through Istanbul, Cappadocia, Antalya, and beyond with interactive maps and street views.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 07:07:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>A Submerged Golden State: Imagining California&#8217;s Future With Rising Seas</title>
		<link>/new-bjhlpy-a-submerged-golden-state-imagining-californias-future-with-rising-seas-rbhkdc-pics/</link>
					<comments>/new-bjhlpy-a-submerged-golden-state-imagining-californias-future-with-rising-seas-rbhkdc-pics/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[2025]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[californias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[future]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[golden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[imagining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[seas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[state]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[submerged]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://w1.geleleger.nl/a-submerged-golden-state-imagining-californias-future-with-rising-seas/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Submerged Golden State: Imagining California&#8217;s Future with Rising Seas Related Articles: A Submerged Golden [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-a-submerged-golden-state-imagining-californias-future-with-rising-seas-rbhkdc-pics/">A Submerged Golden State: Imagining California’s Future With Rising Seas</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Submerged Golden State: Imagining California&#8217;s Future with Rising Seas</p>
<h2 id="related-articles:-a-submerged-golden-state:-imagining-california's-future-with-rising-seas">Related Articles: A Submerged Golden State: Imagining California&#8217;s Future with Rising Seas</h2>
<h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2>
<p>With great pleasure, we will explore the intriguing topic related to A Submerged Golden State: Imagining California&#8217;s Future with Rising Seas. Let&#8217;s weave interesting information and offer fresh perspectives to the readers.</p>
<div id="toc">
<h2>Table of Content</h2>
<ul>
<li><a href="#related-articles:-a-submerged-golden-state:-imagining-california's-future-with-rising-seas">1 Related Articles: A Submerged Golden State: Imagining California&#8217;s Future with Rising Seas</a></li>
<li><a href="#introduction">2 Introduction</a></li>
<li><a href="#a-submerged-golden-state:-imagining-california's-future-with-rising-seas">3 A Submerged Golden State: Imagining California&#8217;s Future with Rising Seas</a></li>
<li><a href="#closure">4 Closure</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2 id="a-submerged-golden-state:-imagining-california's-future-with-rising-seas">A Submerged Golden State: Imagining California&#8217;s Future with Rising Seas</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://b.fastcompany.net/multisite_files/coexist/imagecache/slideshow_large/slideshow/2013/07/1682688-slide-feet-1.jpg" alt="Imagining The Submerged California Coast After The Sea Level Rises  Co " /></p>
<p>The iconic coastline of California, with its dramatic cliffs, sandy beaches, and bustling cities, is a testament to the state&#8217;s unique geography. However, this familiar landscape is threatened by a looming environmental crisis: the melting of the world&#8217;s glaciers and ice sheets. As global temperatures rise, these frozen giants release vast quantities of water into the oceans, causing sea levels to climb. The impact on California, a state with a significant portion of its population and infrastructure located along the coast, could be profound.</p>
<p><strong>Visualizing the Impact: A Submerged California</strong></p>
<p>Imagine a map of California, where the familiar outline of the state is significantly altered. Coastal cities like San Francisco, Los Angeles, and San Diego are partially submerged, their iconic landmarks barely visible above the rising waters. The fertile Central Valley, a vital agricultural region, is transformed into a vast inland sea. The iconic Golden Gate Bridge, once a symbol of human engineering, becomes a submerged ruin. This is not a fictional scenario; it is a stark possibility if global warming continues unabated.</p>
<p><strong>Understanding the Science: Sea Level Rise and California</strong></p>
<p>The rise in sea level is a complex phenomenon driven by several factors, including the thermal expansion of ocean water as it warms, the melting of glaciers and ice sheets, and the loss of land-based ice. The Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC), the leading international body for the assessment of climate change, projects that global sea levels could rise by as much as 1 meter by 2100, with higher levels possible depending on the rate of future warming.</p>
<p>For California, this rise in sea level poses a multifaceted threat. Coastal erosion will intensify, threatening infrastructure, homes, and businesses. Storm surges, already a concern during severe weather events, will become more frequent and severe, exacerbating flooding and damage. The intrusion of saltwater into freshwater aquifers, a vital source of drinking water for many Californians, could compromise water quality and availability.</p>
<p><strong>Beyond the Coastline: The Wider Implications</strong></p>
<p>The impact of rising sea levels extends beyond the immediate coastline. Inland areas will also experience consequences, including increased flooding, salinization of agricultural lands, and disruption of transportation networks. The economic and social implications of these changes are significant, potentially impacting industries like agriculture, tourism, and real estate.</p>
<p><strong>Adapting to a Changing Coastline: A Call for Action</strong></p>
<p>Recognizing the gravity of the situation, California has initiated a range of adaptation strategies to mitigate the effects of sea level rise. These include building seawalls, elevating infrastructure, and investing in early warning systems. However, these measures are often costly and require long-term planning.</p>
<p>The most effective solution lies in addressing the root cause of the problem: global warming. Reducing greenhouse gas emissions through a transition to renewable energy sources, improving energy efficiency, and promoting sustainable practices is crucial to slow the rate of sea level rise and mitigate its impact.</p>
<p><strong>FAQs</strong></p>
<p><strong>Q: How much will sea levels rise in California?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> The projected rise in sea level for California varies depending on the rate of future warming and the contributions of various factors, such as ice sheet melt and thermal expansion. The IPCC projects a global rise of up to 1 meter by 2100, but regional variations are possible.</p>
<p><strong>Q: Will all of California be underwater?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> While the scenario of a completely submerged California is unlikely in the near future, significant portions of the state&#8217;s coastline, including major cities and infrastructure, will be vulnerable to flooding and erosion with continued sea level rise.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What can I do to help?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Individual actions can collectively contribute to mitigating the impact of sea level rise. Reducing your carbon footprint by using public transportation, conserving energy, and supporting sustainable practices can help slow the rate of climate change. You can also advocate for policies that promote clean energy and climate action.</p>
<p><strong>Tips</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Stay informed:</strong> Learn about the science of climate change and the projected impacts of sea level rise in your region.</li>
<li><strong>Reduce your carbon footprint:</strong> Make conscious choices to reduce your emissions, such as using public transportation, cycling, or walking instead of driving.</li>
<li><strong>Support sustainable practices:</strong> Choose products with minimal environmental impact and support businesses committed to sustainability.</li>
<li><strong>Advocate for change:</strong> Contact your elected officials and support organizations working to address climate change and sea level rise.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>
<p>The future of California&#8217;s iconic coastline is intertwined with the fate of the world&#8217;s glaciers and ice sheets. As temperatures rise and ice melts, the threat of rising sea levels looms large, posing a significant challenge to the state&#8217;s environment, economy, and communities. Addressing this challenge requires a collective effort, involving scientific research, technological innovation, and a commitment to reducing greenhouse gas emissions. Only through such concerted action can we safeguard California&#8217;s unique coastline and ensure a sustainable future for generations to come. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://c.fastcompany.net/multisite_files/coexist/imagecache/slideshow_large/slideshow/2013/07/1682688-slide-2-feet.jpg" alt="Imagining The Submerged California Coast After The Sea Level Rises  Co " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://images.fastcompany.net/image/upload/w_1280,f_auto,q_auto,fl_lossy/fc/1682688-poster-1280-venice2.jpg" alt="Imagining The Submerged California Coast After The Sea Level Rises" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://lao.ca.gov/reports/2020/4261/Fig2.png" alt="What Threat Does Sea-Level Rise Pose to California?" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/-gstw44DeSI/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="Sea-level Rise for the Coasts of California, Oregon, and Washington " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://ww2.kqed.org/science/wp-content/uploads/sites/35/2019/03/Sea-Level-Rise-California-Study-800x680.jpg" alt="Sea Level Rise in Bay Area is Going to Be Much More Destructive Than We " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://images.nightcafe.studio/jobs/TNA0CNs4C1gTdWPsHVYc/TNA0CNs4C1gTdWPsHVYc--1--909dp.jpg?tr=w-1600,c-at_max" alt="San Francisco in year 2323, earth is covered in deep water, submerged " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://images.fastcompany.com/image/upload/fc/1682688-inline-venice-beach-at-25-feet.webp" alt="Imagining The Submerged California Coast After The Sea Level Rises " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://www.cakex.org/sites/default/files/Screen%20Shot%202017-07-31%20at%2011.35.11%20PM.png" alt="Map Of Projected Sea Level Rise - California southern Map" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"></p>
<h2 id="closure">Closure</h2>
<p>Thus, we hope this article has provided valuable insights into A Submerged Golden State: Imagining California&#8217;s Future with Rising Seas. We thank you for taking the time to read this article. See you in our next article!</p><p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-a-submerged-golden-state-imagining-californias-future-with-rising-seas-rbhkdc-pics/">A Submerged Golden State: Imagining California’s Future With Rising Seas</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/new-bjhlpy-a-submerged-golden-state-imagining-californias-future-with-rising-seas-rbhkdc-pics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mapping The Rising Tide: Understanding And Addressing The Threat Of Sea Level Rise</title>
		<link>/new-bjhlpy-mapping-the-rising-tide-understanding-and-addressing-the-threat-of-sea-level-rise-rbhkdc-pics/</link>
					<comments>/new-bjhlpy-mapping-the-rising-tide-understanding-and-addressing-the-threat-of-sea-level-rise-rbhkdc-pics/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[2025]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[addressing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[level]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mapping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rise]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[threat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[understanding]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://w1.geleleger.nl/mapping-the-rising-tide-understanding-and-addressing-the-threat-of-sea-level-rise/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mapping the Rising Tide: Understanding and Addressing the Threat of Sea Level Rise Related Articles: [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-mapping-the-rising-tide-understanding-and-addressing-the-threat-of-sea-level-rise-rbhkdc-pics/">Mapping The Rising Tide: Understanding And Addressing The Threat Of Sea Level Rise</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mapping the Rising Tide: Understanding and Addressing the Threat of Sea Level Rise</p>
<h2 id="related-articles:-mapping-the-rising-tide:-understanding-and-addressing-the-threat-of-sea-level-rise">Related Articles: Mapping the Rising Tide: Understanding and Addressing the Threat of Sea Level Rise</h2>
<h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2>
<p>With enthusiasm, let&#8217;s navigate through the intriguing topic related to Mapping the Rising Tide: Understanding and Addressing the Threat of Sea Level Rise. Let&#8217;s weave interesting information and offer fresh perspectives to the readers.</p>
<div id="toc">
<h2>Table of Content</h2>
<ul>
<li><a href="#related-articles:-mapping-the-rising-tide:-understanding-and-addressing-the-threat-of-sea-level-rise">1 Related Articles: Mapping the Rising Tide: Understanding and Addressing the Threat of Sea Level Rise</a></li>
<li><a href="#introduction">2 Introduction</a></li>
<li><a href="#mapping-the-rising-tide:-understanding-and-addressing-the-threat-of-sea-level-rise">3 Mapping the Rising Tide: Understanding and Addressing the Threat of Sea Level Rise</a></li>
<li><a href="#closure">4 Closure</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2 id="mapping-the-rising-tide:-understanding-and-addressing-the-threat-of-sea-level-rise">Mapping the Rising Tide: Understanding and Addressing the Threat of Sea Level Rise</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" src="http://circa.uconn.edu/wp-content/uploads/sites/1618/2016/01/sealevelriseillustration.png" alt="Sea Level Rise  Connecticut Institute for Resilience &#038; Climate " /></p>
<p>The Earth&#8217;s oceans are rising, a consequence of climate change that is reshaping coastlines and threatening communities worldwide. To visualize and understand this complex phenomenon, scientists rely on <strong>sea level rise maps</strong>. These maps serve as critical tools for comprehending the scale of the problem, predicting future impacts, and informing mitigation strategies.</p>
<p><strong>A Visual Representation of a Global Challenge:</strong></p>
<p>Sea level rise maps are visual representations of projected changes in sea level across different regions and timeframes. They typically depict a baseline sea level, often based on historical data, and then overlay projected increases in sea level for specific future dates. These projections are generated through sophisticated computer models that incorporate various factors influencing sea level rise, including:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Thermal Expansion:</strong> As the ocean absorbs heat from the atmosphere, it expands in volume, contributing to sea level rise.</li>
<li><strong>Melting Ice Sheets and Glaciers:</strong> The melting of glaciers and ice sheets, primarily in Greenland and Antarctica, adds significant amounts of water to the ocean.</li>
<li><strong>Changes in Land Water Storage:</strong> Variations in the amount of water stored on land, such as in lakes and reservoirs, can influence sea level.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Understanding the Dynamics of Sea Level Rise:</strong></p>
<p>Sea level rise maps are not static; they are dynamic representations of a complex and evolving phenomenon. They account for spatial variations in sea level rise, highlighting areas that are particularly vulnerable due to factors like:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Land Subsidence:</strong> Some coastal areas are experiencing land subsidence, making them more susceptible to sea level rise.</li>
<li><strong>Tides and Storm Surges:</strong> The combined effect of sea level rise, tides, and storm surges can amplify the impact of flooding.</li>
<li><strong>Coastal Geomorphology:</strong> The shape of coastlines, the presence of natural barriers, and the rate of erosion all influence the vulnerability of coastal areas.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Applications and Benefits of Sea Level Rise Maps:</strong></p>
<p>Sea level rise maps serve a multitude of purposes, providing valuable insights for:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Coastal Planning and Management:</strong> Maps help policymakers and planners understand the potential impacts of sea level rise on infrastructure, ecosystems, and human settlements. This information is crucial for developing effective adaptation strategies, such as relocating critical infrastructure, building seawalls, and implementing sustainable coastal management practices.</li>
<li><strong>Risk Assessment and Mitigation:</strong> Maps enable the assessment of risks associated with sea level rise, allowing communities to prioritize mitigation efforts and invest in appropriate infrastructure upgrades. This includes identifying areas at high risk of flooding, erosion, and saltwater intrusion, enabling proactive measures to minimize potential damage.</li>
<li><strong>Climate Change Research and Monitoring:</strong> Maps provide valuable data for researchers studying the causes and impacts of climate change. They help track the rate of sea level rise, identify regional variations, and assess the effectiveness of mitigation strategies.</li>
<li><strong>Public Education and Awareness:</strong> Maps serve as powerful tools for raising public awareness about the threat of sea level rise. By visualizing the potential impacts, they engage the public in understanding the urgency of climate action and the need for collective efforts to address this global challenge.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>FAQs about Sea Level Rise Maps:</strong></p>
<p><strong>1. What are the different types of sea level rise maps?</strong></p>
<p>Sea level rise maps can be categorized based on their scope, timeframes, and methodologies. Some commonly used types include:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Global Sea Level Rise Maps:</strong> These maps depict projected changes in sea level across the entire planet.</li>
<li><strong>Regional Sea Level Rise Maps:</strong> These maps focus on specific regions, such as coastlines, islands, or continents, providing more detailed information about local impacts.</li>
<li><strong>Static Maps:</strong> These maps present a snapshot of projected sea level rise for a specific future date.</li>
<li><strong>Dynamic Maps:</strong> These maps illustrate the evolution of sea level rise over time, showing how projections change with different scenarios and timeframes.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>2. How accurate are sea level rise maps?</strong></p>
<p>The accuracy of sea level rise maps depends on various factors, including the quality of input data, the sophistication of the models used, and the uncertainty inherent in climate projections. While maps provide valuable estimates, they are subject to limitations and should be interpreted with caution.</p>
<p><strong>3. What are the limitations of sea level rise maps?</strong></p>
<p>Sea level rise maps are based on models and projections, which inherently involve uncertainties. Factors like future greenhouse gas emissions, the rate of ice sheet melt, and the response of the ocean to warming can influence the accuracy of predictions. It is essential to acknowledge these limitations and consider the potential range of outcomes when interpreting map data.</p>
<p><strong>4. How can I access sea level rise maps?</strong></p>
<p>Numerous organizations and institutions provide access to sea level rise maps, including:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA):</strong> NOAA offers a variety of sea level rise maps and resources for the United States.</li>
<li><strong>Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC):</strong> The IPCC provides comprehensive reports and data on climate change, including projections for sea level rise.</li>
<li><strong>Climate Central:</strong> Climate Central is a non-profit organization that develops interactive sea level rise maps and visualizations.</li>
<li><strong>NASA:</strong> NASA provides data and resources related to climate change, including sea level rise maps.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Tips for Interpreting and Using Sea Level Rise Maps:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Understand the Methodology:</strong> Familiarize yourself with the methods used to generate the map, including the models, data sources, and assumptions.</li>
<li><strong>Consider the Timeframe:</strong> Pay attention to the specific future date or time period represented by the map.</li>
<li><strong>Recognize the Limitations:</strong> Acknowledge the uncertainties inherent in climate projections and the potential range of outcomes.</li>
<li><strong>Consult Multiple Sources:</strong> Compare different maps and data sources to get a comprehensive understanding of the projections.</li>
<li><strong>Engage with Local Experts:</strong> Connect with local experts, such as coastal planners or environmental scientists, to understand the specific implications for your region.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Conclusion:</strong></p>
<p>Sea level rise maps are essential tools for understanding the impacts of climate change on coastlines. They provide a visual representation of the complex dynamics of sea level rise, highlighting areas at risk and informing adaptation strategies. By utilizing these maps, policymakers, researchers, and communities can make informed decisions to mitigate the risks of rising seas and build resilient coastal communities. The accuracy and usefulness of these maps will continue to improve as scientific understanding of climate change evolves and technological advancements enhance modeling capabilities. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://www.climate.gov/sites/default/files/DatasetGallery_Sea-Level-Rise-Viewer_thumb_16x9.jpg" alt="Sea Level Rise - Map Viewer  NOAA Climate.gov" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://www.climate.gov/sites/default/files/BAMS_SOTC_2019_sealevelrise_1000px.jpg" alt="Climate Change: Global Sea Level  NOAA Climate.gov" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://oceanservice.noaa.gov/hazards/sealevelrise/thumbnail/ci-dashboard.jpg" alt="Explore: Sea Level Rise" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://climate.nasa.gov/rails/active_storage/blobs/redirect/eyJfcmFpbHMiOnsibWVzc2FnZSI6IkJBaHBBd1JPQWc9PSIsImV4cCI6bnVsbCwicHVyIjoiYmxvYl9pZCJ9fQ==--79d8500733c587411333d6f3dd0773283455ef51/rising-tides-thumbnail.jpg" alt="Rising Tides: Understanding Sea Level Rise – Climate Change: Vital " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="http://i2.cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/120928014853-global-sea-level-changes-story-top.jpg" alt="New satellite data reveals sea-level rise - CNN.com" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://climatecenter.fsu.edu/images/topics/FL_topography.jpg" alt="Sea Level Rise - Florida Climate Center" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://media.news4jax.com/photo/2017/07/25/NOAA-DigitalCoast-map_1501002556938_10161417_ver1.0_640_360.jpg" alt="Rising tides could displace more than 1 million in Florida," style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://climatechange.chicago.gov/sites/production/files/styles/large/public/2016-05/noaaslrtool.jpg" alt="Climate Impacts on Coastal Areas  Climate Change Impacts  US EPA" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"></p>
<h2 id="closure">Closure</h2>
<p>Thus, we hope this article has provided valuable insights into Mapping the Rising Tide: Understanding and Addressing the Threat of Sea Level Rise. We appreciate your attention to our article. See you in our next article!</p><p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-mapping-the-rising-tide-understanding-and-addressing-the-threat-of-sea-level-rise-rbhkdc-pics/">Mapping The Rising Tide: Understanding And Addressing The Threat Of Sea Level Rise</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/new-bjhlpy-mapping-the-rising-tide-understanding-and-addressing-the-threat-of-sea-level-rise-rbhkdc-pics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
