<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>divided - Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks &amp; More</title>
	<atom:link href="/new-bjhlpy-tag/divided/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Discover Turkey’s cities, historical sites, and landscapes on Google Maps. Easily navigate through Istanbul, Cappadocia, Antalya, and beyond with interactive maps and street views.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 01:11:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>A Divided Nation: Understanding The Map Of Civil War America</title>
		<link>/new-bjhlpy-a-divided-nation-understanding-the-map-of-civil-war-america-rbhkdc-pics/</link>
					<comments>/new-bjhlpy-a-divided-nation-understanding-the-map-of-civil-war-america-rbhkdc-pics/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 01:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[2025]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[america]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[civil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[divided]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[map]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[understanding]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[war]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://w1.geleleger.nl/a-divided-nation-understanding-the-map-of-civil-war-america/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Divided Nation: Understanding the Map of Civil War America Related Articles: A Divided Nation: [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-a-divided-nation-understanding-the-map-of-civil-war-america-rbhkdc-pics/">A Divided Nation: Understanding The Map Of Civil War America</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Divided Nation: Understanding the Map of Civil War America</p>
<h2 id="related-articles:-a-divided-nation:-understanding-the-map-of-civil-war-america">Related Articles: A Divided Nation: Understanding the Map of Civil War America</h2>
<h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2>
<p>With enthusiasm, let&#8217;s navigate through the intriguing topic related to A Divided Nation: Understanding the Map of Civil War America. Let&#8217;s weave interesting information and offer fresh perspectives to the readers.</p>
<div id="toc">
<h2>Table of Content</h2>
<ul>
<li><a href="#related-articles:-a-divided-nation:-understanding-the-map-of-civil-war-america">1 Related Articles: A Divided Nation: Understanding the Map of Civil War America</a></li>
<li><a href="#introduction">2 Introduction</a></li>
<li><a href="#a-divided-nation:-understanding-the-map-of-civil-war-america">3 A Divided Nation: Understanding the Map of Civil War America</a></li>
<li><a href="#closure">4 Closure</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2 id="a-divided-nation:-understanding-the-map-of-civil-war-america">A Divided Nation: Understanding the Map of Civil War America</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://www.asaandtheholsteinqueen.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/18.-Civil-War-map-1_final_edited-7.jpg" alt="American Civil War States Map" /></p>
<p>The American Civil War, a tumultuous period in U.S. history, reshaped the nation&#8217;s political landscape, social fabric, and geographical identity. Understanding the map of Civil War America is crucial for comprehending the conflict&#8217;s complexities, its impact on different regions, and the lasting consequences that continue to reverberate in contemporary society.</p>
<p><strong>The Geographic Divide: A Nation Torn Apart</strong></p>
<p>The map of Civil War America reveals a stark geographical divide, separating the Union (Northern states) from the Confederacy (Southern states). This division was not merely geographical but also ideological, rooted in fundamental disagreements over slavery, states&#8217; rights, and economic development.</p>
<p><strong>The Union:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Northern States:</strong>  The Union comprised the 20 free states that remained loyal to the federal government. These states, largely industrial and urban, generally opposed slavery and favored a strong central government.</li>
<li><strong>Key Cities and Regions:</strong>  Important Union centers included Washington, D.C., New York City, Philadelphia, Boston, and Chicago. The Ohio River, a crucial waterway, served as a strategic boundary between the North and South.</li>
<li><strong>Strategic Advantages:</strong> The Union possessed significant industrial capacity, a larger population, and a well-established infrastructure, including railroads and telegraph lines.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>The Confederacy:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Southern States:</strong> The Confederacy consisted of 11 states that seceded from the Union, primarily driven by the desire to protect the institution of slavery and assert their autonomy.</li>
<li><strong>Key Cities and Regions:</strong>  Important Confederate cities included Richmond, Virginia (the capital), Charleston, South Carolina, and New Orleans, Louisiana. The Mississippi River served as a vital artery for the South.</li>
<li><strong>Strategic Advantages:</strong> The Confederacy held a familiarity with the terrain, particularly in the mountainous regions, and relied on skilled cavalry units for defense.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>The Shifting Landscape of War:</strong></p>
<p>The map of Civil War America is not static.  The conflict&#8217;s progression witnessed battles fought across various terrains, from the rolling hills of Gettysburg to the swamps of the Mississippi Delta. The Union&#8217;s strategic objective was to conquer Confederate territory, while the Confederacy aimed to defend its independence and preserve its way of life.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>The Anaconda Plan:</strong>  The Union&#8217;s primary military strategy involved a naval blockade of Confederate ports to cripple its economy and a gradual advance through the South, squeezing the Confederacy like an anaconda.</li>
<li><strong>The Importance of Railroads:</strong>  Railroads played a crucial role in transporting troops, supplies, and communication.  The Union&#8217;s control of key rail lines, particularly in the East, allowed for rapid troop movements and the effective distribution of resources.</li>
<li><strong>The Significance of Key Battles:</strong>  Important battles, such as Gettysburg, Vicksburg, and Antietam, altered the course of the war, impacting the strategic landscape and shifting the balance of power.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Beyond the Battlefield: The Map of Civil War America Reveals Social and Economic Realities</strong></p>
<p>The map of Civil War America also highlights the social and economic realities of the time.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>The Impact of Slavery:</strong>  The institution of slavery was deeply embedded in the South&#8217;s economy and social structure, creating a stark contrast with the North. The war&#8217;s ultimate outcome led to the abolition of slavery, transforming the social and economic landscape of the South.</li>
<li><strong>The Role of Women:</strong>  The war dramatically altered the roles of women in both the North and South. With men away fighting, women stepped into traditionally male-dominated roles, managing farms, businesses, and providing crucial support to the war effort.</li>
<li><strong>The Experience of African Americans:</strong>  The war offered African Americans opportunities for freedom and empowerment. Many escaped to Union lines, seeking refuge from slavery and joining the Union Army to fight for their own liberation.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Frequently Asked Questions about the Map of Civil War America:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Q: What was the significance of the Mason-Dixon Line?</strong>
<ul>
<li><strong>A:</strong> The Mason-Dixon Line, originally a boundary between Maryland and Pennsylvania, became symbolic of the dividing line between the free North and the slaveholding South.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Q: How did the geography of the South influence the war?</strong>
<ul>
<li><strong>A:</strong> The South&#8217;s terrain, with its dense forests, swamps, and mountainous regions, provided natural defensive advantages for the Confederacy.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Q: Why was the Mississippi River so important?</strong>
<ul>
<li><strong>A: </strong> The Mississippi River served as a vital transportation route for both the Union and Confederacy, connecting different regions and facilitating the movement of troops and supplies.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Q: What role did railroads play in the war?</strong>
<ul>
<li><strong>A:</strong> Railroads enabled rapid troop movements, the transportation of supplies, and communication, significantly impacting the war&#8217;s course.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Tips for Understanding the Map of Civil War America:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Visualize the Terrain:</strong>  Use maps to visualize the key battlefields, rivers, and transportation routes, understanding how geography impacted the war&#8217;s progression.</li>
<li><strong>Study Key Battles:</strong>  Research major battles like Gettysburg, Vicksburg, and Antietam, analyzing their strategic importance and the impact they had on the war&#8217;s outcome.</li>
<li><strong>Explore the Social and Economic Context:</strong>  Understand the social and economic realities of the North and South, including the institution of slavery, the role of women, and the experience of African Americans.</li>
<li><strong>Consider the Lasting Legacy:</strong>  Reflect on the war&#8217;s enduring legacy, including the abolition of slavery, the reunification of the nation, and the ongoing debates about the war&#8217;s interpretation and its impact on American society.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Conclusion:</strong></p>
<p>The map of Civil War America is more than a geographical representation; it serves as a visual narrative of a nation grappling with fundamental issues of freedom, equality, and unity. Understanding the map&#8217;s complexities, including the geographical divide, strategic battles, and social realities, is crucial for appreciating the war&#8217;s profound impact on American history and its lasting influence on the nation&#8217;s identity. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://printable-us-map.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/boundary-between-the-union-and-the-confederacy-national-geographic-printable-map-of-the-united-states-during-the-civil-war.jpg" alt="Printable Map Of The United States During The Civil War - Printable US Maps" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="http://thinklikahistoriancivilwar.weebly.com/uploads/2/3/8/6/23866862/_9460133.png" alt="The American Civil War - Map of The Civil War" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="http://image1.slideserve.com/2780387/a-nation-divided-n.jpg" alt="PPT - The American Civil War PowerPoint Presentation - ID:2780387" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.clipartkey.com/mpngs/m/42-421035_map-of-usa-during-civil-war-civil-war.png" alt="American Civil War Battle Maps" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://present5.com/presentation/b7cfe2a0813309f2aa1085e742ec090b/image-34.jpg" alt="A NATION DIVIDED THE CIVIL WAR 1861 -1865" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://artsourceinternational.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/CWA-167.jpg" alt="Civil War Atlas; Plate 167; Map of the United States of America Showing " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="http://www.swanbournehistory.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/Civil-war-map.jpg" alt="Links to the American Civil War 1861-1865 - swanbournehistory.co.uk" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://mrgreenpchs.weebly.com/uploads/5/3/2/5/53254043/a-nation-divided_orig.jpg" alt="Chapter 16: Toward Civil War" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"></p>
<h2 id="closure">Closure</h2>
<p>Thus, we hope this article has provided valuable insights into A Divided Nation: Understanding the Map of Civil War America. We thank you for taking the time to read this article. See you in our next article!</p><p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-a-divided-nation-understanding-the-map-of-civil-war-america-rbhkdc-pics/">A Divided Nation: Understanding The Map Of Civil War America</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/new-bjhlpy-a-divided-nation-understanding-the-map-of-civil-war-america-rbhkdc-pics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Divided Landscape: A Geographical Examination Of The American Civil War</title>
		<link>/new-bjhlpy-the-divided-landscape-a-geographical-examination-of-the-american-civil-war-rbhkdc-pics/</link>
					<comments>/new-bjhlpy-the-divided-landscape-a-geographical-examination-of-the-american-civil-war-rbhkdc-pics/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[2025]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[american]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[civil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[divided]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[examination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[geographical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[landscape]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[war]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://w1.geleleger.nl/the-divided-landscape-a-geographical-examination-of-the-american-civil-war/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Divided Landscape: A Geographical Examination of the American Civil War Related Articles: The Divided [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-the-divided-landscape-a-geographical-examination-of-the-american-civil-war-rbhkdc-pics/">The Divided Landscape: A Geographical Examination Of The American Civil War</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Divided Landscape: A Geographical Examination of the American Civil War</p>
<h2 id="related-articles:-the-divided-landscape:-a-geographical-examination-of-the-american-civil-war">Related Articles: The Divided Landscape: A Geographical Examination of the American Civil War</h2>
<h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2>
<p>With enthusiasm, let&#8217;s navigate through the intriguing topic related to The Divided Landscape: A Geographical Examination of the American Civil War. Let&#8217;s weave interesting information and offer fresh perspectives to the readers.</p>
<div id="toc">
<h2>Table of Content</h2>
<ul>
<li><a href="#related-articles:-the-divided-landscape:-a-geographical-examination-of-the-american-civil-war">1 Related Articles: The Divided Landscape: A Geographical Examination of the American Civil War</a></li>
<li><a href="#introduction">2 Introduction</a></li>
<li><a href="#the-divided-landscape:-a-geographical-examination-of-the-american-civil-war">3 The Divided Landscape: A Geographical Examination of the American Civil War</a></li>
<li><a href="#closure">4 Closure</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2 id="the-divided-landscape:-a-geographical-examination-of-the-american-civil-war">The Divided Landscape: A Geographical Examination of the American Civil War</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://artsourceinternational.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/CWA-167.jpg" alt="Civil War Atlas; Plate 167; Map of the United States of America Showing " /></p>
<p>The American Civil War (1861-1865) was a conflict of immense historical significance, leaving an enduring mark on the nation&#8217;s political, social, and economic fabric.  Beyond the political and ideological clashes, the war&#8217;s geographical context played a crucial role in shaping its course and outcome. This examination delves into the &quot;North and South map&quot; of the Civil War, analyzing the distinct geographical features and their impact on the conflict.</p>
<p><strong>The North&#8217;s Advantages: Resources, Industry, and Infrastructure</strong></p>
<p>The Union, composed of the Northern states, held significant geographical advantages. Its vast industrial capacity, concentrated in cities like New York, Philadelphia, and Boston, provided a crucial edge. The North boasted a robust manufacturing base, producing weapons, ammunition, textiles, and other essential war materials. This industrial superiority enabled the Union to outfit its army effectively and maintain a steady supply of arms throughout the war.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the North&#8217;s extensive railroad network facilitated the rapid movement of troops and supplies. The interconnectedness of Northern cities and towns allowed for efficient communication and coordination, giving the Union a strategic advantage in logistics. The North&#8217;s superior naval power also played a crucial role, allowing it to control key waterways and blockade Southern ports, crippling the Confederate economy.</p>
<p><strong>The South&#8217;s Challenges: An Agricultural Economy and Limited Infrastructure</strong></p>
<p>The Confederacy, comprised of the Southern states, faced formidable geographical challenges. Its economy was primarily agrarian, heavily reliant on the production of cotton, tobacco, and rice. While these commodities were valuable in the global market, they provided little support for a war effort. The South lacked the industrial capacity to manufacture its own weapons and ammunition, forcing it to rely on imports or captured supplies.</p>
<p>The South&#8217;s transportation infrastructure was also limited, with a sparse railroad network and underdeveloped roads. This hampered the movement of troops and supplies, making it difficult for the Confederacy to respond effectively to Union offensives. The South&#8217;s reliance on waterways for transportation also left it vulnerable to Union naval blockades, which severely hampered trade and economic activity.</p>
<p><strong>The Geographic Impact on Military Strategy</strong></p>
<p>The geographical differences between the North and South profoundly influenced military strategy. The North, with its superior resources and infrastructure, could afford to wage a war of attrition, gradually wearing down the Confederate forces. The Union employed a strategy of containment, seeking to blockade Southern ports and isolate Confederate armies.</p>
<p>The South, on the other hand, was forced to adopt a defensive strategy, relying on its knowledge of the terrain and the ability of its soldiers to fight on familiar ground. The Confederacy hoped to exhaust Union resources and secure foreign recognition, ultimately forcing the North to negotiate a peace settlement.</p>
<p><strong>Key Geographical Features and their Impact</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>The Mississippi River:</strong> This vital waterway served as a crucial artery for both sides. The North aimed to control the river, cutting off the Confederacy&#8217;s access to its western territories. The South fought fiercely to retain control, recognizing its importance for trade and communication.</li>
<li><strong>The Appalachian Mountains:</strong> This formidable mountain range provided natural defensive barriers for the Confederacy. The rugged terrain made it difficult for Union armies to advance, allowing Confederate forces to mount effective resistance.</li>
<li><strong>The Atlantic Coast:</strong> The Southern coastline was crucial for both trade and defense. The Union sought to establish a naval blockade, cutting off the Confederacy from foreign supplies. The South defended its ports fiercely, attempting to maintain access to international markets.</li>
<li><strong>The Shenandoah Valley:</strong> This fertile valley in Virginia was strategically important for both sides. The North sought to control the valley, denying the Confederacy a source of food and supplies. The South fought fiercely to retain control, recognizing its importance for agriculture and transportation.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>FAQs: Understanding the Geographical Context of the Civil War</strong></p>
<p><strong>1. How did the North&#8217;s industrial capacity affect the war?</strong></p>
<p>The North&#8217;s industrial capacity allowed it to produce vast quantities of weapons, ammunition, and other war materials. This enabled the Union to maintain a steady supply of arms throughout the war, while the Confederacy struggled to procure necessary equipment.</p>
<p><strong>2. What was the significance of the Mississippi River in the war?</strong></p>
<p>The Mississippi River was a vital waterway, connecting the North and South. Control of the river was crucial for both sides, as it allowed for the movement of troops, supplies, and trade. The Union ultimately gained control of the river, effectively dividing the Confederacy.</p>
<p><strong>3. How did the Appalachian Mountains influence military strategy?</strong></p>
<p>The Appalachian Mountains provided natural defensive barriers for the Confederacy. The rugged terrain made it difficult for Union armies to advance, allowing Confederate forces to mount effective resistance.</p>
<p><strong>4. What impact did the Atlantic Coast have on the war?</strong></p>
<p>The Atlantic Coast was crucial for both trade and defense. The Union sought to establish a naval blockade, cutting off the Confederacy from foreign supplies. The South defended its ports fiercely, attempting to maintain access to international markets.</p>
<p><strong>5. What was the significance of the Shenandoah Valley in the war?</strong></p>
<p>The Shenandoah Valley was strategically important for both sides. The North sought to control the valley, denying the Confederacy a source of food and supplies. The South fought fiercely to retain control, recognizing its importance for agriculture and transportation.</p>
<p><strong>Tips for Analyzing the Geographical Context of the Civil War</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Study maps:</strong> Familiarize yourself with the geographical features of the United States during the Civil War, paying attention to major rivers, mountains, and coastal areas.</li>
<li><strong>Analyze military campaigns:</strong> Examine the strategies employed by both sides and consider how geography influenced their decisions.</li>
<li><strong>Explore the impact of geography on civilian life:</strong> Consider how the war affected people living in different regions, including access to resources, transportation, and communication.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Conclusion</strong></p>
<p>The geographical context of the American Civil War was an integral factor in shaping the conflict&#8217;s course and outcome. The North&#8217;s industrial capacity, superior infrastructure, and control of key waterways provided it with significant advantages. The South, facing challenges in its agrarian economy, limited infrastructure, and reliance on waterways, was forced to adopt a defensive strategy. The conflict highlighted the profound impact of geography on military strategy, logistics, and the overall course of the war. Understanding the &quot;North and South map&quot; of the Civil War provides invaluable insight into the conflict&#8217;s complexities and its lasting impact on the nation&#8217;s history.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="http://thinklikahistoriancivilwar.weebly.com/uploads/2/3/8/6/23866862/_9460133.png" alt="The American Civil War - Map of The Civil War" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://www.swanbournehistory.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/Civil-war-map.jpg" alt="Links to the American Civil War 1861-1865 - swanbournehistory.co.uk" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/6HZ2VgLlHdopnPq0BP7zRwS2Nsk=/0x0:1395x1967/1200x0/filters:focal(0x0:1395x1967):no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/782300/map_20slave_20growth.0.jpg" alt="37 maps that explain the American Civil War - Vox" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/c/c5/US_map_1864_Civil_War_divisions.svg/1280px-US_map_1864_Civil_War_divisions.svg.png" alt="File:US map 1864 Civil War divisions.svg - Wikimedia Commons" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://cdn2.americancivilwar.com/americancivilwar-cdn/tl/1863_west_large.jpg" alt="American Civil War All States Map of Battles" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://monitor.noaa.gov/150th/images/dmap6_lg.jpg" alt="Monitor 150th Anniversary - Civil War History" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://printable-us-map.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/boundary-between-the-union-and-the-confederacy-national-geographic-printable-map-of-the-united-states-during-the-civil-war.jpg" alt="Printable Map Of The United States During The Civil War - Printable US Maps" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="http://paulinascheid.weebly.com/uploads/4/0/6/1/40617297/8622091_orig.png" alt="Map and Timeline - American Civil War" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"></p>
<h2 id="closure">Closure</h2>
<p>Thus, we hope this article has provided valuable insights into The Divided Landscape: A Geographical Examination of the American Civil War. We hope you find this article informative and beneficial. See you in our next article!</p><p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-the-divided-landscape-a-geographical-examination-of-the-american-civil-war-rbhkdc-pics/">The Divided Landscape: A Geographical Examination Of The American Civil War</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/new-bjhlpy-the-divided-landscape-a-geographical-examination-of-the-american-civil-war-rbhkdc-pics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
