<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>paul - Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks &amp; More</title>
	<atom:link href="/new-bjhlpy-tag/paul/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Discover Turkey’s cities, historical sites, and landscapes on Google Maps. Easily navigate through Istanbul, Cappadocia, Antalya, and beyond with interactive maps and street views.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 18:43:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Paul Revere Ride: A Journey Through History And Landscape</title>
		<link>/new-bjhlpy-the-paul-revere-ride-a-journey-through-history-and-landscape-rbhkdc-pics/</link>
					<comments>/new-bjhlpy-the-paul-revere-ride-a-journey-through-history-and-landscape-rbhkdc-pics/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 18:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[2025]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[history]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[journey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[landscape]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paul]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[revere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ride]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://w1.geleleger.nl/the-paul-revere-ride-a-journey-through-history-and-landscape/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Paul Revere Ride: A Journey Through History and Landscape Related Articles: The Paul Revere [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-the-paul-revere-ride-a-journey-through-history-and-landscape-rbhkdc-pics/">The Paul Revere Ride: A Journey Through History And Landscape</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Paul Revere Ride: A Journey Through History and Landscape</p>
<h2 id="related-articles:-the-paul-revere-ride:-a-journey-through-history-and-landscape">Related Articles: The Paul Revere Ride: A Journey Through History and Landscape</h2>
<h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2>
<p>With enthusiasm, let&#8217;s navigate through the intriguing topic related to The Paul Revere Ride: A Journey Through History and Landscape. Let&#8217;s weave interesting information and offer fresh perspectives to the readers.</p>
<div id="toc">
<h2>Table of Content</h2>
<ul>
<li><a href="#related-articles:-the-paul-revere-ride:-a-journey-through-history-and-landscape">1 Related Articles: The Paul Revere Ride: A Journey Through History and Landscape</a></li>
<li><a href="#introduction">2 Introduction</a></li>
<li><a href="#the-paul-revere-ride:-a-journey-through-history-and-landscape">3 The Paul Revere Ride: A Journey Through History and Landscape</a></li>
<li><a href="#closure">4 Closure</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2 id="the-paul-revere-ride:-a-journey-through-history-and-landscape">The Paul Revere Ride: A Journey Through History and Landscape</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://images.squarespace-cdn.com/content/v1/5f189980db5cb01fc34a47f5/1635210083394-Q6QF06QVYMYJU39G2F5I/AC-paul-revere-painting.jpg" alt="The Midnight Ride of Paul Revere — Americana Corner" /></p>
<p>The iconic image of Paul Revere&#8217;s midnight ride, immortalized in Henry Wadsworth Longfellow&#8217;s poem, has captured the imagination of generations. This seemingly simple journey, undertaken on April 18, 1775, holds immense historical significance, marking the beginning of the American Revolution. While the exact route of Revere&#8217;s ride has been debated for centuries, a widely accepted map traces his path, offering a glimpse into the events that unfolded on that fateful night.</p>
<p><strong>Tracing the Path of Freedom:</strong></p>
<p>The Paul Revere Ride map depicts a journey that began in Charlestown, Massachusetts, where Revere, a silversmith and member of the Sons of Liberty, received a coded message from Dr. Joseph Warren. This message, &quot;One if by land, and two if by sea,&quot; signaled the imminent arrival of British troops, destined to seize colonial military supplies stored in Concord.</p>
<p>Revere, along with William Dawes and Samuel Prescott, set out to warn the colonial militia in Lexington and Concord. The map highlights their journey, traversing through the heart of Massachusetts, passing through towns like Charlestown, Medford, Arlington, Lexington, and Concord. Each location holds historical significance, marking key moments in the unfolding drama.</p>
<p><strong>The Significance of the Ride:</strong></p>
<p>Revere&#8217;s ride was not merely a physical journey; it represented a symbolic act of defiance and a crucial catalyst in the American Revolution. His daring mission served to alert the colonists about the impending British attack, allowing them to prepare for the ensuing conflict. The ride itself became a rallying cry, igniting the spirit of rebellion and solidifying the colonists&#8217; resolve to fight for their freedom.</p>
<p><strong>Beyond the Ride: A Legacy of Freedom:</strong></p>
<p>The Paul Revere Ride map serves as a testament to the courage and determination of the colonists. It allows us to visualize the journey, connecting us to the events that shaped the course of American history. This map, along with the historical accounts and artifacts associated with the ride, provides a tangible link to the past, reminding us of the sacrifices made by those who fought for liberty and independence.</p>
<p><strong>Exploring the Route:</strong></p>
<p>The Paul Revere Ride map can serve as a guide for those seeking to retrace the steps of history.  Following the mapped route, one can visit the historical sites mentioned in Revere&#8217;s journey. These sites offer a glimpse into the lives and experiences of the people who lived during this pivotal period. </p>
<p><strong>Lexington Green:</strong> This site marks the location of the first shots fired in the American Revolution. Visitors can see the monument erected in honor of the fallen militia men, and the historic Lexington Green itself, where the first battle of the revolution unfolded.</p>
<p><strong>Concord Bridge:</strong> This bridge was the scene of the first major victory for the colonists. Visitors can see the bridge itself, and the surrounding area, where the British troops were forced to retreat.</p>
<p><strong>The Old North Church:</strong> This church, located in Boston, is famous for its lanterns, which signaled the arrival of the British troops. Visitors can see the church and its iconic steeple, which played a crucial role in Revere&#8217;s mission.</p>
<p><strong>Beyond the Sites:</strong></p>
<p>The Paul Revere Ride map offers more than just historical landmarks. It reveals a landscape rich in cultural heritage, encompassing the colonial towns, rural landscapes, and waterways that shaped the lives of the colonists. Traveling along the route, one can experience the beauty and serenity of these historical settings, gaining a deeper understanding of the context in which the events of the ride unfolded.</p>
<p><strong>FAQs about the Paul Revere Ride:</strong></p>
<p><strong>1. What was the purpose of Paul Revere&#8217;s ride?</strong><br />
The primary purpose of Paul Revere&#8217;s ride was to warn the colonists in Lexington and Concord of the impending British attack. This warning allowed the militia to prepare for the conflict and ultimately contributed to the colonists&#8217; early victories in the American Revolution.</p>
<p><strong>2. What was the route of Paul Revere&#8217;s ride?</strong><br />
The exact route of Revere&#8217;s ride is debated, but a widely accepted map traces his journey from Charlestown to Lexington and Concord, passing through various towns and landmarks along the way.</p>
<p><strong>3. What was the significance of the lanterns in the Old North Church?</strong><br />
The lanterns in the Old North Church served as a coded signal to Revere, indicating the mode of British troop arrival. &quot;One if by land, and two if by sea&quot; meant that the British troops were arriving by sea, prompting Revere to take the longer route to Lexington and Concord.</p>
<p><strong>4. What happened to Paul Revere after his ride?</strong><br />
Following his ride, Paul Revere continued to play a significant role in the American Revolution. He served as a military officer, participated in the Boston Tea Party, and later became a successful businessman.</p>
<p><strong>5. What is the best way to experience the Paul Revere Ride?</strong><br />
There are various ways to experience the Paul Revere Ride. One can follow the mapped route, visiting the historical sites along the way. Alternatively, there are guided tours available, offering insights into the historical context and events of the ride.</p>
<p><strong>Tips for Exploring the Paul Revere Ride:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Plan your route:</strong> Utilize the Paul Revere Ride map to plan your journey, ensuring you visit the key historical sites along the way.</li>
<li><strong>Research the history:</strong> Familiarize yourself with the events of the ride and the historical context surrounding the American Revolution. This will enhance your understanding and appreciation of the journey.</li>
<li><strong>Engage with the sites:</strong> Take time to explore the historical sites, reading the information boards and engaging with the exhibits. This will allow you to connect with the events of the ride and gain a deeper understanding of the historical context.</li>
<li><strong>Consider a guided tour:</strong> Guided tours offer valuable insights into the history and significance of the ride. They can provide context and anecdotes that enhance your understanding of the events.</li>
<li><strong>Enjoy the landscape:</strong> The Paul Revere Ride route passes through beautiful landscapes, offering a chance to connect with the natural world and appreciate the environment in which the events of the ride unfolded.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Conclusion:</strong></p>
<p>The Paul Revere Ride map serves as a powerful reminder of the events that shaped American history. It allows us to visualize the journey, connect with the historical sites, and appreciate the courage and determination of those who fought for freedom and independence. By retracing the steps of history, we gain a deeper understanding of the past and its enduring legacy. This journey, marked by historical landmarks and a rich cultural heritage, offers a unique opportunity to engage with the past and reflect on the enduring spirit of liberty that continues to inspire generations. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://paulreveresride.weebly.com/uploads/5/7/6/4/5764392/3428290_orig.jpg" alt="Maps - Paul Revere&#39;s Ride" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="http://paulreveresride.weebly.com/uploads/5/7/6/4/5764392/17647_orig.gif" alt="Maps - Paul Revere&#39;s Ride" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://api.army.mil/e2/c/images/2014/04/18/341091/max1200.jpg" alt="Paul Revere rides into history, 18 April 1775  Article  The United " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="http://d28hgpri8am2if.cloudfront.net/tagged_assets/cvr9781604334937/9781604334937_hr.jpg" alt="Paul Revere&#39;s Ride  Book by Henry Wadsworth Longfellow, Charles " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="http://www.thomaskingsleytroupe.com/wp-content/uploads/FOTWH-Paul-Revere.jpg" alt="A Fly on the Wall History: Paul Revere’s Ride  Thomas Kingsley Troupe" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://i0.wp.com/cms.sofrep.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/Paul-Reveres-ride.jpg?fit=1000%2C659u0026ssl=1" alt="Paul Revere Begins His Famous Ride on April 18, 1775" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://cdn.theatlantic.com/thumbor/NX8dAWYDsQxfmlERmI561C0Ga0U=/56x285:2941x1908/1952x1098/media/img/2017/02/AP_46010101780/original.jpg" alt="Paul Revere’s Ride - The Atlantic" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://www.revolutionary-war.net/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/paul-revere-ride-montgomery-the-beginners-american-history-1904-wcpd-1.jpg" alt="The Midnight Ride of Paul Revere  Facts, Full Text &#038; History" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"></p>
<h2 id="closure">Closure</h2>
<p>Thus, we hope this article has provided valuable insights into The Paul Revere Ride: A Journey Through History and Landscape. We appreciate your attention to our article. See you in our next article!</p><p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-the-paul-revere-ride-a-journey-through-history-and-landscape-rbhkdc-pics/">The Paul Revere Ride: A Journey Through History And Landscape</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/new-bjhlpy-the-paul-revere-ride-a-journey-through-history-and-landscape-rbhkdc-pics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Map Of Minneapolis St Paul</title>
		<link>/new-bjhlpy-map-of-minneapolis-st-paul-rbhkdc-pics/</link>
					<comments>/new-bjhlpy-map-of-minneapolis-st-paul-rbhkdc-pics/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 11:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[2025]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[map]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[minneapolis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[paul]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[st]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://w1.geleleger.nl/map-of-minneapolis-st-paul/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>map of minneapolis st paul Related Articles: map of minneapolis st paul Introduction In this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-map-of-minneapolis-st-paul-rbhkdc-pics/">Map Of Minneapolis St Paul</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>map of minneapolis st paul</p>
<h2 id="related-articles:-map-of-minneapolis-st-paul">Related Articles: map of minneapolis st paul</h2>
<h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2>
<p>In this auspicious occasion, we are delighted to delve into the intriguing topic related to map of minneapolis st paul. Let&#8217;s weave interesting information and offer fresh perspectives to the readers.</p>
<div id="toc">
<h2>Table of Content</h2>
<ul>
<li><a href="#related-articles:-map-of-minneapolis-st-paul">1 Related Articles: map of minneapolis st paul</a></li>
<li><a href="#introduction">2 Introduction</a></li>
<li><a href="#navigating-the-twin-cities:-a-comprehensive-guide-to-the-minneapolis-st.-paul-map">3 Navigating the Twin Cities: A Comprehensive Guide to the Minneapolis-St. Paul Map</a></li>
<li><a href="#closure">4 Closure</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
<h2 id="navigating-the-twin-cities:-a-comprehensive-guide-to-the-minneapolis-st.-paul-map">Navigating the Twin Cities: A Comprehensive Guide to the Minneapolis-St. Paul Map</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" src="https://www.gifex.com/images/0X0/2009-09-18-10636/MinneapolisSaint-Paul-City-Map-Minnesota-United-States.jpg" alt="Minneapolis/Saint Paul City Map, Minnesota, United States - Full size" /></p>
<p>The Minneapolis-St. Paul metropolitan area, often referred to as the &quot;Twin Cities,&quot; is a vibrant hub of culture, commerce, and innovation. Understanding the geographic layout of this region is essential for navigating its diverse neighborhoods, exploring its iconic landmarks, and appreciating the tapestry of life that unfolds within its borders.</p>
<p><strong>Understanding the Twin Cities&#8217; Geography</strong></p>
<p>The Twin Cities are situated in southeastern Minnesota, nestled along the banks of the Mississippi River. Minneapolis, the larger of the two cities, lies on the west bank of the river, while St. Paul, the state capital, occupies the east bank. The two cities are separated by the Mississippi River and connected by numerous bridges, creating a seamless urban fabric.</p>
<p><strong>Key Features of the Minneapolis-St. Paul Map</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>The Mississippi River:</strong> This iconic waterway serves as the dividing line between Minneapolis and St. Paul. It flows through the heart of the Twin Cities, providing scenic views and recreational opportunities.</li>
<li><strong>The Chain of Lakes:</strong> A series of interconnected lakes, including Lake Calhoun, Lake Harriet, and Lake of the Isles, form a picturesque chain in Minneapolis. These lakes offer opportunities for swimming, boating, and enjoying the natural beauty of the city.</li>
<li><strong>The Downtown Core:</strong> This bustling area encompasses both Minneapolis and St. Paul, with skyscrapers, cultural institutions, and vibrant nightlife.</li>
<li><strong>The Suburbs:</strong> Surrounding the Twin Cities are a network of suburbs, each with its own unique character and amenities. These suburbs offer a range of housing options and community environments.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Navigating the Map: Essential Landmarks and Neighborhoods</strong></p>
<p><strong>Minneapolis:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Downtown Minneapolis:</strong> Home to the iconic IDS Center, the Minneapolis Convention Center, and the Guthrie Theater, this area is a hub of business, entertainment, and culture.</li>
<li><strong>Uptown:</strong> Known for its vibrant nightlife, eclectic shops, and trendy restaurants, Uptown is a popular destination for young professionals and families.</li>
<li><strong>Northeast Minneapolis:</strong> This area boasts a thriving arts scene, with galleries, theaters, and music venues. It also features the historic Mill City District, home to the ruins of the Washburn A Mill, a testament to the city&#8217;s industrial past.</li>
<li><strong>South Minneapolis:</strong> This diverse neighborhood is home to the University of Minnesota and offers a mix of residential areas, commercial districts, and cultural institutions.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>St. Paul:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Downtown St. Paul:</strong> The state capitol building, the Science Museum of Minnesota, and the Cathedral of St. Paul are just a few of the notable landmarks in this historic area.</li>
<li><strong>Summit Avenue:</strong> A prestigious residential street lined with stately mansions, Summit Avenue is a testament to St. Paul&#8217;s rich history.</li>
<li><strong>Lowertown:</strong> This vibrant neighborhood is known for its art galleries, live music venues, and historic architecture.</li>
<li><strong>West Seventh:</strong> This trendy district offers a mix of restaurants, bars, and boutiques.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Exploring the Map: Transportation and Connectivity</strong></p>
<p>The Twin Cities boast a robust transportation network that includes:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Metro Transit:</strong> This public transportation system operates buses, light rail, and commuter rail lines, connecting residents and visitors to various parts of the metropolitan area.</li>
<li><strong>Interstate Highways:</strong> Interstate 94, Interstate 35W, and Interstate 394 are major highways that traverse the Twin Cities, providing access to surrounding areas.</li>
<li><strong>Minneapolis-St. Paul International Airport (MSP):</strong> This international airport serves as a major transportation hub for the region.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>FAQs about the Minneapolis-St. Paul Map:</strong></p>
<p><strong>Q: What is the best way to get around the Twin Cities?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> The Twin Cities offer a range of transportation options, including public transportation, ride-sharing services, and private vehicles. Metro Transit provides an extensive network of buses, light rail, and commuter rail lines. For short-distance travel, ride-sharing services are convenient and readily available.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What are some must-see attractions in the Twin Cities?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> The Twin Cities are home to a wealth of attractions, including the Minnesota State Capitol, the Walker Art Center, the Science Museum of Minnesota, the Guthrie Theater, and the Mill City Museum.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What are the best neighborhoods for families in the Twin Cities?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> Many neighborhoods in the Twin Cities are family-friendly, offering excellent schools, parks, and recreational opportunities. Some popular family-oriented neighborhoods include Edina, Wayzata, and Minnetonka.</p>
<p><strong>Q: What are the best neighborhoods for nightlife in the Twin Cities?</strong></p>
<p><strong>A:</strong> The Twin Cities offer a vibrant nightlife scene with a variety of bars, clubs, and live music venues. Some popular nightlife districts include Uptown, Northeast Minneapolis, and West Seventh in St. Paul.</p>
<p><strong>Tips for Navigating the Minneapolis-St. Paul Map:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Utilize online mapping tools:</strong> Websites and mobile apps such as Google Maps and Apple Maps can provide detailed directions and real-time traffic information.</li>
<li><strong>Explore different neighborhoods:</strong> The Twin Cities offer a diverse range of neighborhoods, each with its own unique character and attractions.</li>
<li><strong>Take advantage of public transportation:</strong> Metro Transit provides an efficient and cost-effective way to get around the city.</li>
<li><strong>Plan your route in advance:</strong> Traffic congestion can be a challenge in the Twin Cities, especially during peak hours. Planning your route in advance can save you time and frustration.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Conclusion:</strong></p>
<p>The Minneapolis-St. Paul map is a gateway to a dynamic and multifaceted urban landscape. Understanding the geographic layout of the region allows residents and visitors alike to navigate its diverse neighborhoods, explore its iconic landmarks, and appreciate the rich tapestry of life that unfolds within its borders. Whether you are a seasoned resident or a first-time visitor, the map serves as an invaluable tool for discovering the unique charm and vibrant energy of the Twin Cities. </p>
<p><img decoding="async" src="http://static2.bigstockphoto.com/thumbs/0/9/3/large1500/3907944.jpg" alt="Minneapolis - St Paul Metropolitan Area Map Stock Photo &#038; Stock Images " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://www.creativeforce.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/12/minneapolis-st-paul-metro-map1.jpg" alt="Minneapolis &#038; St Paul Metro Map  Digital Creative Force" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://c8.alamy.com/comp/C2EM32/map-of-minneapolis-st-paul-and-minnesota-C2EM32.jpg" alt="Map of Minneapolis, St. Paul and Minnesota Stock Photo - Alamy" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://i.redd.it/2orsmvwj1zx31.jpg" alt="Official map of Minneapolis &#038; St. Paul - 1923 : r/Minneapolis" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="http://travelsfinders.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/08/search-stp.jpg" alt="Minneapolis St. Paul Map - TravelsFinders.Com" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="http://toursmaps.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/08/minnesota-map.jpg" alt="Minneapolis St. Paul Map Tourist Attractions - ToursMaps.com" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"><br />
<img decoding="async" src="https://www.alamy.com/aggregator-api/download?url=https://c8.alamy.com/comp/2JM7GDB/administrative-and-road-map-of-saint-paul-minnesota-united-states-2JM7GDB.jpg" alt="Administrative and road map of Saint Paul, Minnesota, United States " style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"> <img decoding="async" src="https://media.davidrumsey.com/rumsey/Size4/D5005/5840141.jpg" alt="Map Of Minneapolis Saint Paul - Maping Resources" style="width: 200px; height: 200px;"></p>
<h2 id="closure">Closure</h2>
<p>Thus, we hope this article has provided valuable insights into map of minneapolis st paul. We hope you find this article informative and beneficial. See you in our next article!</p><p>The post <a href="/new-bjhlpy-map-of-minneapolis-st-paul-rbhkdc-pics/">Map Of Minneapolis St Paul</a> first appeared on <a href="/">Explore Turkey on Google Maps: Cities, Landmarks & More</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/new-bjhlpy-map-of-minneapolis-st-paul-rbhkdc-pics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
